Hello and welcome.
My name is zayd.
I'm an ethical hacker a computer scientist and I'll be your instructor in this course and this goes
should go and learn how to use your Android device and penetration tester so you'll be able to use a
phone or a tablet in order to hack into computers phones tablets or any computer system really even
networks the really cool thing about using your Android device is first of all it's more portable than
a laptop.
Can if you're walking into a company or an organization you're going to look much less suspicious using
your Android device than using a laptop.
Also there is a large number of social engineering attacks that you can do and you can perform by simply
connecting your Android device to the computer or to the network that you're trying to hack.
So I'm going to start with you from scratch.
So the first thing you're going to learn is you're going to learn how to prepare your Android device
for penetration testing.
I'm going to show you what programs that you need to install and how to set up the whole operating system
to use it and penetration testing was done with that.
We're going to move into our first section which is information gathering in which you're going to learn
how to gather information about Web sites computers networks or anything that exists around you.
Once done with that we're going to move into our two most fun sections which is the spying and the exploitation
sections and the spike section.
You're going to learn how to spy on computers and networks.
So we're going to learn how to become the man in the middle using a number of methods and what this
basically means is that you will be able to capture anything sent or received from your target computer.
This means you'll be able to capture usernames passwords or anything your target computer does.
We're going to be able to achieve this wirelessly or by connecting your Android device to the target's
computer using the U.S. cable once done with that.
We're going to move on to the exploitation section.
Where are you going to learn how to gain full control over computer systems.
So again you'll be able to gain control over any computer that's in your network.
You'll also be able to gain control over computers by simply connecting your Android device using the
US cable.
You'll also see how you can bypass logon screens.
So if your target computer uses Marcos or Windows and it's locked so you need to enter a password to
use a computer.
We'll see how you can bypass that by simply connecting your Android device to that to that computer
at the end of the cursor will also cover some security features that you can do or precautions that
you can do in order to protect yourself from these kind of attacks.
Now all the attacks explained in this course are real attacks performed against real computers in my
lab.
So they're not proof of concepts or attacks that actually work.
The course is highly practical.
But before we do any attack we'll actually learn how it works theoretically and then we're going to
move in to the practical side.