Now we're going to talk about how you can protect yourself against poisoning attacks if we go back to
how they are proposing a works.
And we just have a look on them.
If you remember the way they work is by exploiting two major security flaws and they are few protocols.
So the first one is that each day our fuel costs our response is trusted.
The second one was is that their clients accept responses even if they did not ask for it.
So when I go to the router and I tell when I got to the client and I tell him I am the router and he's
going to believe me straight away and when I go to the router and tell him I am the client he's going
to believe me again.
Now the way I tell the router and the client that I'm a different person.
So the way I spoof my identity is by I tell that the target device have a different MAC address.
So when I want to tell the router that I am the client I tell him the person with the client IP has
my MAC address.
So as the AARP table that the router has the MAC address of the client is going to change to one.
And when I do it to the client so I'm going to tell the client the MAC address of the router is my MAC
address.
So the MAC address for the router at the client RPE table is going to change.
So the first way to detect a are people using a tax is only by looking at your ARPU tables.
So if I go here to my target device and I go to a RPA and we saw this in the first month in the middle
with young we're talking about ARPU poisoning we can see the MAC address for the router.
So answer with one if you want to.
Now when I do my AARP attack subs are going to do a simple ARPU poison.
Same way that we always do it is going to turn.
And if I go back to the time machine and I go RPA as you can see here I have the MAC address for the
target device for the target for the router has changed so still the router has this IP but his MAC
address is actually now the attackers Michaela.
So this is if I go to the Ground Zero you'll see that this is the same address that shown up here as
the routers MAC address.
The router is actually my address is this so this is an easy way of detecting what they are proposing
is happening when you're you're being poisoned.
Another way so this is this is very handy and very simple.
But you won't be able to be doing this all the time to check if you're being poisoned or not.
So an easier way is to use a tool that was actually my 30 or AARP tables.
And whenever something happens whenever something such suspicious happens it's going to give me a warning.
So I'm just going to make sure everything is back here.
So when I stop the attack you can see the MAC address is back to the normal MAC address.
So we're going to have an honor to get to have a look on a tool called X HRP.
Now this tool works on Linux on Windows and as you can see you just run the tool.
And even if I close it here.
So this is a basic security to go undetected and get close it's still it's going to run in the background
here and I'm going to go back to Cali and I'm going to do another ARPU poison.
Now this is we can only see one group here so I'm just going to quit it and do it again.
As you can see the two groups and now I have my two groups.
I'll go here.
As you can see we have another
and they alerted us that the MAC address of 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 1 which is the router has changed to something
else.
Now we can also from here we can see that the device that has this MAC address or the device that the
MAC address of there are has been changed to.
Is it connected devices and other device with me on the network and it has this IP.
So now we actually know this is the attacker because this device is Mac.
And the author's apparent MAC address.
This is a spoofed MAC address are the same.
So now we actually know that 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 11 is the person who is trying to do a R.P. poisoning on
our network.
Now these methods only work on your own device so if another device is being they are people isn't so
if there is another device on my network it's been poison.
I want to be able to detect it this way because this only monitors my own HRP table that doesn't it
doesn't have any access to anyone else's HRP table.