An other way to discover people and they get tax and other suspicious behavior and the network is to
use wireshark.
So let's first of all find Wireshark.
I'm going to enable one feature here if I go on settings
protocols HRP and detect RPE requests so I'm going to think that that's basically going to detect whenever
a device tries to discover all connected devices.
So whether the attacker is using wireshark or net discover or auto scan whenever a device tries to detect
all connected devices wash outskirt be able to detect that.
That's because this device is going is going to try to go through each eyepiece so it's going to go
on 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 1 1 2 1 3 1 4 and it's going to send packets asking if that if there is a device exists
on these IPs.
So we're going to go on our Wi-Fi card and I'm not going to do what they are proposing.
Now I'm just going around net discover.
So just like right before we're going to use our wireless card and then I'm going to put my rage
over 24 and that's it it's finished.
I discovered everything.
Now if we go back we actually don't even need something to tell us or give us a warning as we can see
here that it's asking for who has we can see that the MAC address of the target the source is the MAC
address of our attacker machine and it's asking about each single IP so I was asking about 33 to 33
34 something from one like ants going all the way up and asking if there is a device on this IP.
Now if you go and analyze and we go on the ex-parte tempo if we go on the notes you'll see that we have
our peers packet's term have been detected which is basically some devices trying to detect all connected
devices.
Let's go back here and we're going to do and they are people isn't normal they are poisoned like we
always do it going to enter and the devices were entirely correctly so I'm just going to do it again.
And the groups are OK now so we'll go back to here.
So if we go on analyze the expert info you'll see that we have another warning here and that's a double
digit IP address for 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 1 which means that the router appears to have two Mica addresses
and this can never happen because each device should have 1 1 MAC address.
So we know that someone is trying to poison us here again.
So that's the three methods that would help us detect they are poisoning attacks.
Now if we go let me just go here and I'm going to go and run
and RPA This is my RPE table so as you can see that these entries are dynamic.
That means that they can change and they're allowed to be changed.
So one way of completely protecting your network against our people is allowing attacks is to use static
IP tables and static IP tables.
And trees are not allowed to be changed so once you actually put on and configure the market was for
the router for example.
That can never be changed.
Therefore when someone tries to poison your device and spoof the MAC address of the router.
This is not going to work because you have a static table that its value can never be changed.
The only problem with using static IP tables is that you're going to have to configure the AARP tables
in each device every time there's a new device connects to the network because because they're static
they're not going to be accept any changes to them.
Therefore you're going to have to manually configure each one of them whenever there's a new device
to connect network.
But it's a solution to completely protect yourself or your network against it.
It's hard to implement and large that works well on smaller networks.
It's as can be implemented it can be done and it completely completely protect you against people visiting
attacks.