It the next few classes we're going to talk about an attack called Bad USP.
Man in the middle attack and this attack we're going to use our Android device and physically plug it
in into the target device used in the US pre-cable.
Now you usually do that to charge the device or to transfer data between the devices.
So you're going to go when you're going to plug in your Android device to the target's computer.
And once you do that our Android device.
And so they've stolen the computer that it is a media device or that is it is a phone it's actually
going to tell the computer that it is a network device.
Not only that but it's also going to force all the traffic going to and from the target's computer to
go through our Android device.
This means that all user names all passwords all of you are elves or chat messages.
Everything that the target computer is going to do.
And whenever it tries to access the Internet it's going to do that through our device or it's going
to it's going to use our Android device as a network card and send all the requests and responses will
be flowing through our Android device instead of making them flow through its internal Wi-Fi card or
wire card or ethernet or whatever.
So basically our Android device is going to be used as a network card and all the packets all the data
will be flowing through with the Android device.
Now in order to set the device in that way we have to do a few steps.
So let's go to the kallah device and see how we can do this now you can actually do this using the Kalli
menu.
But for some reason the menu is not working for me.
That's why I'm going to be doing it from the terminal.
So let's see how we can actually do it from the terminal.
So I have my Android device here and I'm going to go to the hunter home and I'm not going to go through
the menu so you can actually go here to the but you SBM out in the middle attack and start the attack
from here.
Well it's not working for me so that's why I'm actually just going to launch a terminal and I'm going
to do the attack from the terminal.
Now the first thing that I'm going to do is navigate to SD card
files so CD is just the command to change the working directory.
Now I have a file there and the resources you can download it yourself.
I call that a flush IP tables.
Basically this file contains a number of commands that will clear all the rules are there and the IP
tables IP tables is just a firewall that's used in Linux.
Now some rules might cause our device to draw packets because it'll see them as a threat.
So what we want we want the packets to flow through our device and we wanted to act as a network and
therefore I have a few comments in that file that will basically just delete all rules that you might
have in your IP tables.
So to execute that just download the file from the resources and executed using this command Bash and
put the name of the file which is flush
IP tables that SH And because you don't see any error messages that means everything was executed successfully.
Now the next thing that we want to do is run WSP attack run the attacks that fuels the target computer
that this is a network card when we connect it to the target computer so well I'm going to do is brush
and just put the name of the file.
It's another.
Again it's another script but this script comes in with Nat hunter so you don't need to download it
just right like this.
So it starts but USP
kids can't do it.
SH No if you have Android 5 use the lollipop one since I have kids cost four point four point four.
So I'm using Kit-Kat and I'm going to hit enter and because you don't see any error messages I guess
that means everything was run successfully.
So now the attack is working on the device.
And once I connected the device using the U.S. cable it's going to fool the computer that it connects
to.
Now I forgot to mention this this attack should work on Windows and the next box and I'm going to be
running it on Linux now and in the future I'll be in a similar attack and I'll run that on Windows just
to show you that they both work on both operating systems.
So I'll show you here I'm actually connected to my network here to to
go running.
This is this is just to show you that how the IPs are going to change so you actually don't need to
do this when you're running the attack.
So I'm just going to run.
I'm sorry ifconfig.
And I'll show you what is.
So this is the IP address my current IP address and my current network.
And as you can see that's the one that's being used to connect to the Internet.
So I'm going to connect my Android device this device device that's been mirrored here I'm just going
to connect it physically to this computer.
So it's connected now.
And as you can see I've got a message here telling me that I got connected to using a wired connection.
So this is the only way that a person can actually get suspicious as as long as soon as this message
disappears then they won't notice it.
Now if we actually go on a Iran if conflict again I'll show you how the IP changes now.
And as you can see now I have an extra card now if conflict shows you the network that you have the
commands that I just ran here.
So as you can see that I have an extra card connected and an extra network connected.
It has this IP address.
So basically now anything I'm going to do on this computer will be throw a flowing through this Android
device so any user names that I put on the internet and your passwords and your messages and your Else
everything is going to be flowing through this nexus device the Nexus device will execute the request
and send it back to our device.
So everything is going to be working but it's going to be flowing through this device which makes it
the man in the middle which means that all the packets will be flowing through this device and we can
read them we can modify them and we can do whatever we want with them.
Now let's just confirm that I actually have internet connection so I'm just going to run a browser here.
I'm gonna go to being dot come and as you can see I do have Internet connection and everything is perfect.
Both the packets are actually flowing through this device.
And the next class is now.
We'll see how we can actually capture these packets save them in a file read them modify them and we'll
see what kind of stuff we can actually do with them.