OK.
So now that we are the man in the middle and all the packets are flowing through this device we're going
to see how we can save all the data that gets sent into our file and we'll see how we can open the file
or read it and read passwords usernames or you or else whatever that's been sent by the target person.
So what we're going to do we're going to use a tool called shark shark will basically just save all
this data in a file and then will read the data used in a tool called Wireshark.
So first things first will start capturing detailed data using the shark so the shark.
And after I usually put the wires in the device that you want to capture capture data from and in our
device or NDIS zero and then put the file name that you want to store the data in and I'm going to call
it capture one.
And as you can see it's in it's capturing data on our NDIS zero so that's perfect.
Now I'm going to go to my browser on Chrome and I'm going to maybe just go to some Web sites maybe just
run a search for anything for cars.
I'm going to search for a Web site called pretty site mob generate term I'm going to click on the Web
site and I'm going to log in now I want to show you or I want you to note that this Web site doesn't
use TTP.
So it only uses CTP as you can see there is no lock icon here so it only uses HTP.
So this username and password will be sent through TTP.
Therefore we will be able to capture them without seeing any warnings.
So the target person as you can see this is here.
The target person will not see any error messages when they log in.
Now the target website uses Hastey tips as such as the big Web sites such as Yahoo Hotmail Facebook
Google all of them.
They use Hastey CPS.
Therefore if I try to navigate them their Web sites now I'll actually see a warning.
And even if I don't see a warning I will not be able to read the username and password because they
will be encrypted so what I'm going to do now here I'm just going to log in on and his Web site and
in the future I'll show you how we can bypass Hastey CPS.
So for now we're just going to log in we're going to say maybe the user name is zayd.
It's who that has come I'm just going to use fake username and password.
I'm going to put the password one two three four five six.
Enter now I didn't log in but this this data has been sent and it should have been captured by our sniffer
here so I'm going to do.
I'm just going to start capturing to do a Control-C using the Android or using the terminal on Android.
You need to hold the volume down button and press.
So as you can see that simulator control see and that terminates any running program.
So if I do ls to list the current files us should see a file called Capture.
So what I'm going to do here I'm going to send that file into my laptop now so we can analyze it.
Now there are you can just open it using apps on Android but it's really hard to see through the packets
through the packages.
And the reason you'd be using your Android anyway is just as a stealth method to steal usernames and
passwords.
So you'd want to be able to plug it in somewhere get it to capture data and then when you go home open
the file and read what's in there.
So that's exactly what I'm going to do.
I'm actually going to send this file to my laptop and read it from the laptop and analyze it.
So I'll just show you the file that we just captured our working directory was as D-CT files.
So I'm in SD card here and I'm going to go to files and we should see a file called Capture as you can
see this is it captured on.
So I'm just going to send this file to my laptop and we'll see how we can analyze it using Wireshark.
Right so I'm going to open Wireshark
and wireshark is available on Windows and Linux and can be used to do sniffing and it can be used to
just analyze packets.
We will be using it in multiple classes and you will get used to how to use it and how to deal with
it.
So I only want to open the file that we captured using our Android device.
So I'm going to go on file and open and here I am in the downloads because I just downloaded the file
and it's called Capture One Cup.
As you can see.
I'm going to open it and here are all the packets that were sent and received by our targets computer.
So let's just have a look on these packets now.
The main important part of what a shark is the source destination.
So the source is where the packet is going from and destination is the IP where it's going to protocol
is the protocol length is the size and the info is just other info about the packet.
So as you can see here for example we can see that the person was trying to access WWE.
When you go being dot.com
here you can see that there were requests made to send dot com.
You can use this part to filter the packets.
So right now I'm actually looking for the username and password so I'm only going to look for it if
packets and I'm just going to type unhedged TTP and enter and that will filter and it'll only show me
Hashd TTP packets.
Another thing you can do is just click on the info and it will organize packets for you by their info
so I'm actually looking for posts because usually when you put a username and password they're actually
sent to use in post.
So I'm just going to scroll down until I find a post request sent
and we can see that we have all the post requests here.
And this one is interesting because it says User Control Panel.
So I'm going to click that one and I'm going to come here.
I'm going to go on the line bays and as you can see that we can we have here is the use the action was
a log in the e-mail is Zayd at yahoo dot com.
And the password is 1 2 3 4 5 6.