So far we've seen how we can capture usernames and passwords using our Android device only by connecting
it to the target computer.
Now the only problem is that if the person tries to logon to a Web site or uses his shitty POS such
as Yahoo or Hotmail to bypass that we're going to use a tool called SSL Strip.
Now as a sales rep is not going to decrypt SSL or do anything like that.
Oh it's going to do is downgrade and he hates it if he has connection to hasty t.p.
So when you pose for example log in Dot yahoo dot com you automatically go to the hashtag CPS version
of that Web site.
What SSL strip is going to do is going to detect that and it's going to redirect you to the Haitian
version.
The target person will not see any warnings and you will be able to capture the username and password
the same way we did before because essentially the connection is not shitty anymore.
It's just TTP.
So in order to do this we're actually going to need to run two commands.
The first command is just an IP tables command.
As I said IP tables is just a firewall and Linux firewall and this command is going to redirect any
packet on port 80 is going to redirect it to port 10000.
We do this because SSL strip runs by default on port 10000.
So you can change the port that Sellstrom runs on and all they have to do is just change this command
and get it to redirect to strip port.
Once you run this command you are going to run SSL strip.
Basically SSL so then it's going to listen whenever he's actually CBS is going to downgrade it to TTP.
So let's see how we do this.
So we have our Android device here again and I'm going to start sniffing just like I did last time and
I'm going to call the file capture to this time
OK.
Enter.
And here we go we're capturing packets now.
So the next thing we're going to do is run the two commands that I just showed you to run as a small
strobe.
So I'm just going to go and open up a new terminal window
so it's window to right here and we're going to run our IP tables come on so IP tables
and I have the command here just written in the file so I'm just going to copy and paste it
in and turn on because there is no errors that means the command has worked successfully and the next
thing we're just going to run SSL strobe
and wind speed to tell it to only log on you work on the post requests.
They're usually the post requests of the ones that are used to log in.
So where are you going to.
Or are you trying to get usernames and passwords so we only wanted to work on post requests.
So everything is working now everything's perfect.
I'm going to go on my target which is this device and we're going to try to go to mail at yahoo dot
com and try to logon.
Now I'd like you to note that this Web site is not actually CPS it's normal hey CTP as you can see here.
There's nice utopias.
So that means SSL Strip has worked successfully.
Now if you look at my android window you actually see some warnings here but that's OK.
You get these anyway but it's working.
So I'm going to log in to my username I'm just going to say again Zayd let's say something else or to
say to you who is Garmin going to put a password this time I'm going to put nine eight seven six five
four I'm going to enter that.
Again these are wrong usernames and passwords I'm just using them to demonstrate the attack.
I'm also going to go to Mount.
I'm going to log in I'm going to call it a hotmail took out come and say the password is Hotmail pass.
Again wrong usernames and passwords just for demonstration.
So now we logged in.
I'm going to do the same as what we did before.
So I will stop capturing here.
I'm actually going to stop as the cell strip controls the volume down and see and then I'm going to
start capturing here.
And I'm going to go to my file manager right here.
And we should see a file called Capture to here.
And as you can see it right there.
So I'm going to send this file to my laptop.
I'm going to open it and Wireshark and we'll try to analyze it and see our usernames and passwords.
OK I downloaded the file now and I'm going to run Wireshark.
And just like before I'm going to go file open and we have our captures to here I'm going to open it.
And again just like before.
I'm going to firster by his TTP and it's already organized in them by the info so I'm just going to
scroll down to post.
Actually it's not.
So I'm going to click on info.
I'm gonna scroll to posts.
And we have three four post requests that have been sent by our target.
So let's look at the first one.
And we're going to look at the line based on as you can see I was trying to log in with a user name
called they too and the password nine eight seven six five four.
Let's look at the other one and the other one.
As you can see here this is the ultimate one.
So it was a hot melt at hotmail dot com and the password was Hotmail POS.
Now I said so strip works to bypass safety CPS.
The only problem with it these days is that it does some Web sites like Google and Facebook are using
a new technology called hater's ts.
Basically what that does is it will not serve you the web site unless it is a hasty tibias Web site.
So it wants to review a DTP Web site or DTP version of that Web site.
Therefore SSL strip does not work against these against Gmail and Facebook right now if you're using
Chrome browser songy Chrome browser supports it and only Facebook and Google are using it at the moment.