So far we've seen how we can read data and read sensitive data like usernames passwords you or else
all that kind of stuff when we are the man in the middle.
Now I spoke about modifying the packets.
So what we're going to see today is something called DNS spoofing DNS spoofing will allow us to redirect
any requests to to our domain to another domain.
For example if someone requests Facebook dot com we carried direct them to Google we carried them to
Yahoo.
We carried them to our fake Facebook page.
We carried them to our Facebook page that contains a Trojan and their entire computer.
We can redirect them to our own server.
We can redirect them to any place that we want the attack is very simple and it works just because we
are the man in the middle.
So once we run a program called DNS spoof we will configure it in a way that once it sees a certain
domain it will redirect or it will send a different response to the target person.
So I'll run the attack and you'll actually it will become clearer how it works.
When I run the attack.
So first of all we're going to create a configuration file.
So I've already made one here by the way.
I'm using a free file manager called as file manager.
It's really handy as you can see it here can download it from the App Store or from the Play Store and
what I have here I have my DNS spoof configuration file.
So I just have it's called DNS spoof right here.
So I'm going to open it as text using the text editor.
And as you can see it's very simple.
The first part of the file as you can see here I specify the IP address that I want to redirect to.
And the second part.
We put the domain that we want to hijack or that we want to spoof.
So any time a person or the target person tries to access Facebook dot com they will be redirected to
this you are out or to this IP address.
Now how this works I'm going to run a program called DNS spoof and I'm going to tell the program to
work according to this configuration.
So the program whenever it sees that there is a pocket lock in for Facebook the come.
It's going to go to this IP address get the Web site that is running on this IP address and send it
instead of sending Facebook to come.
Simple as that if your eyes are the 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 1 0 you can change that to any IP you want.
This is the Web site where Facebook is going to be spoofed.
Now we have this particular address because I have a web server running here so I wanted to do this
using my own web server to show you that you can actually put anything there.
That web server.
And we will be doing stuff like that in the future.
We will be using fake Web sites or fake pages so you can actually just put a fake page on this web server.
And then they're going to see it instead of seeing the actual page.
For now I just have a basic just a hasty M-L page for a demonstration in this class.
But in the future as I said we will be doing more advanced of.
So the web server is running here on another virtual machine this virtual machine as I call it in this
machine.
Again you don't have to do this you can redirect to anywhere you want.
I'm just doing it here to show you.
So this is actually al-Khalil the next machine.
So Candy we're using our version of card on our Android device but there's also a Kalli distribution
that you can install as a virtual machine or as a main machine and it has all the tools that you need
for penetration testing.
So I'll just show you here what I have or what's going to redirect to.
So bar W.W. that's where the server is.
And I basically just have an index attached Well just a normal Hastey page that just says yolo.
Now you can change this to anything you want.
As I said we're just doing a demonstration here so you should actually start the server.
The web server on your machine.
Again you don't have to do this if you're using another IP address and I'll show you that this is the
machine that we're going to redirect to.
So as you can see this is the IP of the machine and that's what we are redirecting to here.
And our Android device.
So the configuration is done as you can see.
Now all we have to do and we are already in the middle because we're using about us we attack.
So all I'm going to do is just go back to my terminal and I'm going to run DNS spoof.
So DNS
you put the interface.
So our interface is or and is zero and you put the configuration file that we just created.
The file is stored and as the card
files
DNS
now DNS spoof is running.
Let's go try to access Facebook and see what happens.
And as you can see I got redirected to a page just saying yolo.
As I said you can change this to whatever you want.
And you can see here that this doesn't change so it's still saying it's going to Devante them to the
windows.
Facebook does come but we are not in Facebook we went somewhere else.
So this can be used to serve a fake Facebook page and wife has haziest.
Yes.
So if the target person was using hate Yes you can just create yourself a fake Facebook page and get
him to log in to that from here and this way you'll be able you want to decrypt and haters to hate.
Yes but you'll be able to redirect him to a fake page and gain access to their username and password.
You can also get them to download something and that will be a backdoor you can do a lot of things with
DNS spoofing.
And we will see how useful it is and how we can use it in different attacks.