Welcome to the first section of our course and this section we're going to be talking about weaponized
in your Android device.
So we're going to talk about how what the programs that you're going to need to install on your Android
device so that you can use it as a penetration testing to the main program or the main software that
we need to install is called Net hunter and that Hunter is an Android operating system or a flavor of
Android does come in with a number of programs pre-installed that are used for penetration testing that
Hunter is free so you can download it for free and install it and it's supported on all access devices.
So that's Nexus 4 5 6 and 7 at the moment.
And the one plus there are other versions for other Android devices but there are not officially supported.
So the only devices that are supported officially are the nexus and the one plus installing that Hunter
is very simple we have to do a few things first before we can install it first we're going to have to
install the drivers on our computers so that the computer can recognize our Android device.
Then we're going to unlock the device.
And we're going to route it route is basically an account that has the highest privileges and Linux
systems.
So androids actually built on Linux and because of that we need to install a root account on it.
The router can't because it has the highest privileges it allow us to do or to gain full control over
the device so we will have full control over the hardware and we will be able to run specific tasks
that we cannot run without the router account.
Then we're going to install net hunter which is the modified Android draw ramp that contains all the
programs that we need for penetration testing.
This whole process is very simple.
It's not as complicated as it seems.
And we're going to see how we can do it in the next lectures.