Now I'd like to show you the love that I'm going to be using during this course.
So basically I have my calendar.
As I said it's installed or not hunter is installed on a Nexus 7 device.
I have the device here mirrored on my laptop.
I'm doing this because it's easier to show you what I'm doing on a device like this and sort of using
a camera because I'd lose quality.
So this is actually this is not a virtual machine.
This is a physical Android device that I'm using and this is just programs that I'm using to measure
the screen of the device.
And here I have my windows device who will going to try to how kids may be hacked passwords or usernames
or stuff from this account.
So this is a virtual machine thumb it makes an actual real machine.
This is an actual physical Nexus 7 device that has nets Hunter installed on it.
And this is my main operating system.
So let's just have a quick look on that Hunter home.
So this is it's icon right here so I'm going to click it now and as you can see you just get the basic
welcome screen where you see your wireless cards and you can request your external life.
You can click on that.
I'll get my external IP if we go here on the top left.
You'll see all the menus that you can go.
Basically this whole menu allow you to access all features for that hunter.
So within this menu you can navigate and run multiple attacks.
So if we just go to the first one the Culdee luncher you'll see a number of options that you have here.
So the first one launch can the shell and terminal basically will give you a terminal window where you
can use all the programs that come installed with that Hunter so tough that
it's going to it's going to ask me to granted access the root access and I'm going to say there's no
problem.
And as you can see now I have my access and I can run any programs that I want to run from within this
menu.
Now we will be using this and you're right now I'm not going to run anything because that's not our
lesson.
We're just going to have a quick look on everything that we can do.
We will be using this later.
So I'm just going to close it to go back decal them in here.
The second option gives you a terminal menu that allow you to run a number of programs.
So as you can see right here we have a number beside each program that we want to run and you can just
put the number that you want and it's going to take you to different menus and it's going to allow you
to run different accounts.
Again I'm not going to be using this right now because this allows you to run a number of programs and
we will be using it in the future.
I'm just showing you how this works.
So I'm going to close it again.
The third one.
Launch boy fights Why fight is a wife.
Penetration testing.
And the second option is going to update Carly second US is going to turn off if we have an external
wiper.
It's going to turn it off.
And the last one will unwiped.
So the first one actually lunch Kelly and terminal.
The last one will unmount.
Kelly
the service control this allows you to turn services on and off.
So these are servers that come in preinstalled on net hunter and you can turn them on and off using
these options.
So you have the framework S-sh DNS dnsmasq and all these kind of servers topit to turn it on.
So S-sh is not what's up.
And if you turn it on top it again it goes off again.
I will be talking about what each one of these mean.
And when we will need to use them right now we're just having a quick look.
After that we have the A-H I.D. keyboard talk and I'm not gonna talk about it right now.
We'll going to have a full class about or maybe actually more than one class about this.
Same with th id Durkee attacks and WSP man in the middle attacks man.
Evil likes point.
All of these were actually going to spend more than one lunch lecture talking about them.
So I'm going to ask Kip all of these here and the last to allow you to configure IP tables and yet DNS
mosque.
Again I will be talking about each one of these later so don't be scared of other names or the number
of features that you can see here.
Right now we're just having a quick look on the launcher menu.
So the main the main parts of this class is you can Roncalli you can run features from all features
from within this window.
You can Roncalli in terminal you can run the menu in terminal as well which allow you to run a number
of programs.
We're going to be using all of this for multiple times within the course so it's going to become very
easy and it's going to expand itself even more as we progress through the course.