So usually after you gather enough information about your target then you are ready to carry out the
attack that you want to do.
So in the next in this section the spying section and then the next section the exploitation.
We're going to talk about how you can actually launch attacks to achieve your goals.
Now on the spying section we're going to be talking about attacks that allow us to get user names passwords
chat messages any type of sensitive information that might be useful to you.
We're going to talk about three main methods to become the man in the middle as you can see we have
three big circles each one of them represent a different way of becoming the man in the middle.
Now what I mean by becoming the man in the middle is being in the middle of the connection between your
target and the source of the requests.
So in most of the cases is the server.
So when you are the man in the middle or the requests and the response is going to and from the target
machine will be combing through your device.
So your request to any Web site any username and password any chat message anything Argles person does
will be sent to your device then to the Internet.
And when it comes back it comes to your device then to the target person.
Now as I said we're going to be talking about three different methods to achieve that and why that device
starts treating you as a man in the middle is different depending on the method.
Once you're the man in the middle you can read user names you can reach passwords so you can read all
kind of packets.
You can also intercept the packet so you can modify them.
So for example of a person is downloading a file you can get him to download a different file without
them even knowing if they request Facebook dot com you can't take them somewhere else with a fake Facebook
log in you need to do that because you got to be able to get the usernames and passwords anyway.
You'll be able to sniff cookies you'll be able to sniff passwords usernames you are Elle's images anything
that goes through the target person and between you after you are the man in the middle we're going
to talk about different attacks and different scenarios so you can mix and match these attacks.
So for example if I spoke about a few attacks that you can do using WSP method you can actually do them
when you're IRP poisoning.
So the method of becoming the man in the middle is irrelevant.
So these small circus circles represent the attacks that you can do after becoming the man in the middle.
And you can do them regardless of the method that you use to achieve becoming the man in the middle.
Also with this section some of the attacks that we're going to learn in this section we're actually
going to carry them out in the next section into bigger scenarios to show you how we can gain full access
to computers using different methods.