So the three main methods that we're going to use to become the man in the middle are the bad USV man
in the middle attack HRP poisoning and evil access point.
So the bad US man in the middle attack will basically allow you to become the man in the middle by connecting
your Android device to the target's laptop or to the computer.
Once you do that the Android device is going to fool that computer that it is a wireless or that is
a network card.
Once it does that it's also going to force all the traffic through the Android device.
So instead of your laptop for example when you go to Google dotcom it's going to use your wireless card
or your wild card and use the means of connection whether you're connected via wire or wireless go to
the router ask for Google.
Bring it back when you connect your Android device to it.
It's actually going to think the card is your Android device.
So when it wants to go to Google dot com it's going to send it to your to your device then your device
using 3G or use an another wireless card will go get Google does come and give it back to the computer.
So your device is the man in the middle.
All the packets will be flowing through your device therefore you can read intercept or modify them.
Again we're going to talk about this in more detail.
And the attacks that you achieve after that you can mix them or you can do them with other man in the
middle attacks.
It doesn't really matter how you become the man in the middle wants or the man in the middle you can
do these attacks anyway.
The second method is used and they are poisoning.
This is a bit more complicated but it's explained in diagrams.
And once you actually understand it it's really simple at the start it's hard to get your head around.
But once you actually go through the lessons it's going to be very simple very powerful very useful
at that.
This is very powerful and useful because you don't need to physically connect to your Android device.
It literally works because of a flaw in a.
And the AARP protocol.
So we're going to talk about this and we can understand how this works.
Once you can actually do this you can run it into you can write on Wired and on wireless networks it's
very powerful and works on all operating systems.
So it is very very useful.
The bad us we attack also works on all operating systems windows and X and Mac and the third method.
We're going to talk about is the evil access point.
So in this method we're actually going to create a wireless network.
So we're going to use our Android device the same way when you do tethering.
So when you tether your 3G connection to help a friend to access the Internet.
Exactly.
We're going to tether the Internet connection into on our Android device can do it again using 3G or
using Wi-Fi.
And if you're getting use wife again the two cards and I'm going to explain that.
So we're basically going to create an access point.
For example you can call it free internet.
When people connect to this access point you're automatically the server.
So automatically when they want to go to any Web site they're going to send you the request and when
you get the request you're going to send their response to them.
So automatically you are the man in the middle and the packets will naturally flow through your device
which means that you can read intercept and modify them.
Again all of these attacks we're going to talk about them in more detail and we're going to talk about
what you can do after you become the man in the middle and in the next section will actually see how
we can mix this with other exploitation methods to gain full access to the target's computers.