This class and the next few classes we're going to learn about AARP poisoning our people is and it is
just another method of becoming the man in the middle.
And a network in previous videos we so how we can use the bad USP attack where we physically connect
our Android device to a laptop or to a computer.
And by doing that we force all the traffic through our device which makes us the man in the middle.
Once we the man in the middle.
We were able to intercept packets read them modify them drop them do all that kind of fun stuff.
Now another method of becoming the man in the middle is using ARPU poisoning.
This is one of the most dangerous dangerous and effective attacks.
It's very dangerous because you don't need to interact with the target device or at least the user will
not see that interaction.
So you're not going to need to physically plug your device you're not going to need to send anything
to the user.
You will be interacting with with the target device was all that interaction is going to happen in the
background so that the target person will not feel it will not even know that anything has happened.
This attack is possible because when AARP protocol was programmed or made them people did not pay attention
to the security side of the protocols.
So it's very simple it's very effective but it's not secure.
Therefore the attack is possible on all network enabled devices.
So whether the as long as the device uses DARPA protocol then you can attack that device using this
method.
So whether it's a phone a tablet or computer running Windows Linux iOS Marcos it doesn't matter as long
as it uses ARPU which all of them does.
Then you can use HRP poisoning to become the man in the middle without sending anything to the target
device without interacting with the user and without physically interacting with the device.
So let's understand and see how this attack works.
This is just a normal network.
And let's assume this is your home network.
So you have a device here.
That's the target device that we are trying to attack whenever it needs requests for example whenever
it needs to access Google or Yahoo or anything it sends the request to a server.
So the server this is your local router.
So it doesn't matter whether you're connected on Wi-Fi or use an Ethernet you're always connected to
a router.
So you're going to or a server in the network.
So you're going to send your request to the server the server is what is connected to the Internet so
it's going to go.
It's going to go to the Internet.
It's going to get you Google dot com then it's going to give you the reply back and then you'll have
Google does come on your computer.
Now the problem with they R.P. is that each request or response is trusted.
So whenever you send requests and whenever you send a reply you receive a response you always like computers
always trust Data response or request so they don't identify or they don't verify the source where they
got the request from.
And this is going to come clear now and the next step.
So say for example when this device sent something to the router install it tell him that I am computer
number one for example the router is going to trust that this is computer number one without verifying
that this is actually computer number one.
The second problem is that the devices can actually accept responses without sending or request so this
device can actually accept responses even without sending requests.
So for example it can actually just get a response tell on him tell on this device something some information
and this device not only is just going to accept it it's also going to trust it.
It's not going to verify the information in there.
It's not going to verify the source of information.
So these are the main problems with HRP protocol.
So since we can send responses and the device is going to trust whatever information sent in that response
we're going to send our response to the target device tell them that that I tell them that device that
I the router now because the device except responses is going to accept that response and because it's
not going to verify my identity it's going to trust me and it's going to treat me as thereafter now
the way I tell him that I am there router by just telling him that the MAC address of the router has
changed.
And this is the new MAC address.
Now the MAC address as we said it's physical.
It never changes show so it should always be the same but it's going to trust it here.
It's not going to even think about anything as long as I send a response because ARPU trusts everything
it's going to trust the response that I sent.
Now the next step we're going to do.
We're going to send another response to the router this time telling the router that I am the target
device.
So the router whenever it needs to send something to this device it's actually going to send it to me
instead of sending it to that device again because it accepts responses and because it doesn't verify
what information is there it's going to accept that and it's going to treat me as this device.
Now once we do this twice we've actually redirected the flow of packets.
So every time this device wants to do something it's going to think that I am the router.
So it's going to send the request to me.
Well I'm going to do I'm actually going to send the request to the router.
The router is going to go get me the request send it back to me because it thinks that I am this device
and then I'm going to forward that request to the target device.
So as you can see it's actually very simple.
Two main issues with the protocol allow us to exploit our protocol and redirect the flow packets which
causes us becoming the man in the middle and ones who are are the man in the middle.
We can actually do all the attacks that we saw before and we'll see how we can do them in a different
way.
Now in the next lectures.