So let's go now and see how we can actually run and IRP spoofing attack we're going to use a tool called
AARP spoof which is part owners who called this nerve.
We've already used one tool of this Neph which was DNS spoof we use that to carry out a DNS spoofing
attack with the bad USP.
Today we're going to use a piece proof to carry out an RPG poisoning attack this tool is very popular.
It's very easy to use and can be used from terminal and it's ported to most operating systems including
an iOS Android backoffice Windows Linux everywhere.
That's why I'm going to explain it in this lecture once we actually use it.
And this lecture we're now going to use it in next lectures we're going to use in something simpler
simpler but it's really handy to know how to use a piece proof.
I'm just going to show you here.
I'm actually going to clear this window and I'm going to do a RPA to show you the AARP table.
This is our target machine here.
And you can see that my IP address for the access point or for the router or for the server is this
and the MAC address is this.
And this is how the spoofing is going to happen.
So once we actually do the AARP poisonings you will see that this MAC address changes to the address
to the MAC address of my card or my wireless card on my Android device.
So I'm going to go back here to my Android device and I'm going to launch my terminal
before I determine terminal.
I want to show you here that the name of my wireless card here as you can see is non-zero.
And my IP address is this.
We're not going to need the IP address but the name is non-zero.
So I'm going to launch Culley terminal
I'm going to excuse
I'm going to put my wireless card name after this which is 9 0 and then I'm going to put my targets.
So we're actually going to execute this command twice the first time we're going to be poisoning the
client or the target device.
And then the next time we're going to be poisoning the access point or the server and the first time
we're going to be telling the the client that I'm the router or I am the server.
And the second term we're going to be telling the server that I am the target device.
This was going to put us in the middle of the connection.
So we're going to do this using the IPs.
So I'm going to put the IP of the server which is 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 1.
And then I'm going to put the IP of my target device which is let's just have a look on it here.
So I'm just going to do I think
as you can see this is my IP address.
So 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 2 4 1 want to put it back
and that's Ed and I'm going to run my second I'm not going to execute this right now.
I'm just going to type in my second month
and the difference between this and the other one is that we're going to just change this to one and
we'll change the other one to two for one
and that's going to be my second command.
And then the third command that we're going to run is just to allow the packets to flow through our
mouth through my device so that it doesn't drop the packets because if we don't do that then packets
will become they will come to my device and then the device will just drop them thinking that they cause
a threat.
So what we want to do we want the packets to flow through the device and we want our device to act like
a router.
So we're going to enable IP forwarding which is done using this command.
OK so all my commands are ready now I'm just going to execute them.
And before I do that I'll just go back and do the RPA to show you here.
Right.
So let's do our first command and hit enter.
And that's going to poison my client telling him that I am the router then I'm going to go do this and
tell the router that I am the client.
So now I should be in the middle and I'm going to do this earth command to allow packets through flow
through my device and not drop them.
Now I should be the man in the middle.
And to verify that this is the target device that we are targeting I'm going to run a RPA to show the
MAC address and notice the change here.
So we're still using the same IP for the router.
What this device thinks the router has this MAC address.
So as you can see it used to be this one and it was changed to this one.
And also note that this is the same MAC address for device have an IP 17.
So only by running a RPA you can actually see that this device with this IP is trying to do our people
isn't it.
Because it has the same MAC address as the router.
Now since our device since this device thinks we are the router anytime it tries to access any Web site
it's going to send the request to this device which is actually my Android device.
So that's going to place me in the middle which means that I'm going to be able to read draw up modify
the packets.
So right now you're actually the man in the middle.
You can do the tasks that we did use in WSP attacks.
You can go ahead and run teeshirt to sniff the packets.
You can run SSL strip to strip them and bypass Hastey CPS and you can run DNS spoof to do DNS spoofing.
You can do the scenarios that we did and we're going to do.
So basically are now the man in the middle you can do all the man in the middle attacks that we learned
before and do all that kind of fun stuff.