Now that we know how to do IRP spoofing and becoming the man in the middle using a sharpie spoof we're
actually not going to use it anymore.
As I said we're going to use a tool called Zanti to now actually use this before to discover all the
connected devices.
We're going to see now how how to use it to do it in the middle attacks using HRP poisoning.
So the first thing that we're going to see is how to sniff usernames and passwords.
We did this before using the bad USPO attack with T-Sharon.
Again you can actually use T-shirt.
And here with a Arpey spoof like we did before and sniff usernames and passwords.
But as I said now we're going to use another tool which actually makes it much easier.
So I'm going to run Zanti to here.
As you can see it's already discovered all the devices and as you know we're actually attacking the
windows device today.
So this is the Windows device here so I'm just going to tap it and then I'm going to go to the man in
the middle attacks here.
And I'm just going to turn this on right now.
Turn off the cell strip for now.
I'm going to turn this on and that will do a Arpey poisoning and place me in the middle of the connection.
So that's go here.
We'll just verify that by do and our P.A. And as you can see that the MAC address is changed to my MAC
address in my Carol-Lee Linux or in my NAT Hunter device.
So that means that the attack was executed successfully.
So I'm going to go to being dot com like we did before with the bad us we attack and then I'm going
to go to free site generator again because this all uses TTP.
I'm going to log in with a fake account.
Just any name so I'm going to say Zayde.
Who does.
Com password.
One two three four five six.
Antar
and back here on our Nat Hunter device.
I'm going to go on view log requests
and as you can see here we can see the websites that were accessed.
So we can see that we accessed the Mozilla that network site which is Firefox's Web site.
And then we accessed domain of Google and then we accessed three sitemap generators here.
And as you can see here with we have accessed Bing dot com and as you can see here for a free site map
generator it's in yellow so it's highlighted for us and it says that we have one password in here so
that's what I meant.
It's easier like you don't need to open the packets file in Wireshark like we did before.
So I'm just going to tap this here and I'm going to swipe to the right to the passwords and you can
see that the user name was Zayde at Yahoo dot com.
And the password is 1 2 3 4 5 6 and the user was trying to access every site map generator control panel
OK now you can swipe left to get the request so you get all the posts and get requests that we heard.
You can get the user agent so we can actually we know now the user uses Mozilla Firefox 5 so you can
again go ahead and look for exploits for this particular browser and try to attack that browser.
I'm going to go back right now and show you another feature of Zanti which is a cell Strip.
Now we saw before how we can do that manually how to how to use SSL strip manually.
That's why I actually like to teach you how to do stuff manually first because these ARBs and these
tools they do work well and they're nice but sometimes they fail.
So if you know how to do that stuff manually you can go ahead and do it manually.
If these apps fail.
So I'm just tap in here on SSL strip and says that it's on.
So we should be able to if we go to mailboat Yahoo dot com we should go to the normal Yahoo and not
the U.P.S. one.
And we should be able to sniff the username and password.
So I'm going to do that.
I'm going to mail that here.
Who can.
As you can see here on top we didn't go to the hasty tips one so we should be able to sniff this user
name and password.
So again I'm going to go again with Zayde going call the two at Yahoo dot com and the password I'm going
to make it.
Nine eight seven six five four now.
And again let's go back here.
Go on the you logged requests and as you can see again the Web site has come on in yellow.
We Tirpitz it so nice that there is one password navigate the passwords and you can see that the user
name is zayd and the password is what.
Nine eight seven six five four.
I really like the way this filters the username and password and makes it so easy to read and access.
This is the whole point of using your mobile.
You want to do stuff quickly so you either just save it on a on a file and analyze it from your laptop
or you want something like this that just gives you the information really quick.
Another feature that I want to show you and this video is just capturing the images.
So let's just go to images that yahoo dot com and just search for anything so just say Kurds or whacko's.
Now we go back to our device and I'm going to stop on logged images.
And as you can see you can actually see all the images that showed up or that the person the target
person have seen or like accessed on his browser.
So just another easy nice feature to see.
Now you can also do DNS spoofing use in Zanti.
The only problem with DNS spoofing here is that it redirects all hash TTP to the target that you specify.
So you can't actually just redirect one Web site.
It's going to redirect all web sites or all requests to the website that you're going to put in here.
So that's why we're If you want to do DNS spoofing you're going to have to do with the same way we did
it with the bad you and the with the bad USPO attack because that way we can actually only hijack one
website or one domain which will make it more difficult to the target to know that they are being attacked
and it's also more professional and smarter because redirecting all the traffic is just really easy
to discover that you're actually trying to attack that person or that website.
So again if you want to do DNS spoofing I don't recommend using Zanti you can just go and do with the
same way we did it with the USPS tag.
You just have to enable the Arpey poisoning here or do it with a piece proof like we did in Delight's
lecture and then do it with DNS spoof.