OK so we're still doing man in the middle and they are poison and using Zanti.
And I'd like to show you one of the really cool features of Zanti this feature will allow us to capture
any downloads.
The target person does so whenever they download any file will be able to capture it and downloaded.
So I'm just going to enable here capture downloads and I'm going to choose the type of file that I'd
like to capture and it's going to be zip files now I'm going to go into the target device and download
and Ziv
So I'm just going to go ahead and look for something with Zip extensions so we have here I'm going to
download it.
Save it.
So it's called 7 8 9 0 0 going to it.
OK.
Now Zanti should actually capture that and save it for me.
Now all this stuff will be downloaded to SD card.
So let's go to our file manager here and see if it actually was downloaded.
So we have Zanti captures here.
As you can see that I have my file right there so I can open it and see what's in there and it is the
actual exactly the same file.
So I'll just verify that for you here.
It went in downloads or you can just open it here.
And as you can see it's the same file.
We managed to capture that.
Now it's even cooler from intercepting downloads is or capturing downloads is replacing a downloaded
file with something else.
So for example let's imagine that the target person is trying to download some of axes some program.
We can actually replace that program with a virus or a backdoor or anything that we want.
So that's when the target person runs their program they actually run our backdoor so I'm going to go
down and going to go on intercept downloads and enable that then I'm going to go on the settings.
I'm going to change it to XP and then I'm going to select the X-C that I wanted to replace this stuff
with.
And I have a calculator here that I'm going to use.
So now whenever a person tries to download any cxi file it's going to be replaced with what I selected
here which is a calculator.
So let's go here and I'm going to download 7 zip for Windows and the XP version.
So I'm going to save that file and it's saved.
Now why we want this.
This should be a calculator and it should not be normal.
So has a file.
So I'm going to run it.
And as you can see I got a calculator and instead of getting 7 zip.
Now this is huge.
We can actually use it in the future scenario.
So this way you can actually backdoor any file that the target person downloads.
So you're not going to be trying to send the person and trick them into downloading a file and then
when they're on the file you get what you want you're going to just create your backdoor or virus or
Kilowog or whatever it is and just wait for the target person to download something once they download
that thing from under official website that they trust and they will want to run that program because
they willingly downloaded it when they run it.
They'll actually run your virus or your program instead of running the actual program that they downloaded.