And this video and I were going to have on some of the other features of Zanti which is their place
and images so we saw how we can replace files.
You can also replace images
you can select the image that you want to replace stuff with.
So I'm just going to choose the color the next image right here and it's already enabled.
So if I go back to my yahoo search for images and search for something all the images there will be
replaced by what I selected.
So the search for cars for example.
So as you can see all the images that are loading here are the same image that we picked for in next
which means that all the images are being replaced with what we want.
Again you can think of multiple ways to exploit this to yourself.
We're not actually doing exploitation as you noticed before even on replacing the downloaded files.
We didn't do the full exploitation thing because I'm leaving that to the exploitation part of the course.
So we're only learning how we can do this how we can do it in the middle how we can do all that stuff.
And then in the future we'll see how we can combine these attacks to fully exploit our target machine.
So I'm going to disable this now and I'm going to show you the last feature of Zanti which is certain
HDMI code.
Now this can be really useful to replace parts of pages that we want or to do access attacks which basically
allow you to steal cookies.
It's really simple.
You just tap on the on and then you put DHHS all access code or restaged them H.M.S. code that you want
to execute in here.
And then here on the target machine if you just go anywhere this code will be executed.
So I'm just going to go to you who does come and then you'll see an alert coming up which is the code
that we added it should show on and Artane Zanti test as you can see Yahoo website Donne's doesn't say
that.
So the code was executed again you can do this to do multiple accesses attacks but I'm not actually
going to go deep into that because it's really not very it is useful in other situations.
But if you are the man in the middle you can do much more powerful attacks than this.