And this lecture we're going to learn another method in becoming the man in the middle.
Now in the previous lectures we saw how we can use the bad US attack to force the traffic through our
device.
One we physically connected to any device that allows us to read all packets modify them and do whatever
we want with them because essentially all the traffic that is sent or received to the target device
will be going through our device.
And we also learned how to do IRP poisoning which allowed us to become the man in the middle as well
and we were able to do the same attacks so we can run with the bad USV attack because again the packets
will be flowing through our device.
Today we're going to learn another way of becoming the man in the middle.
This is actually really simple we're going to create an access point.
So it's the same way that sometimes you use your phone to to share your 3G connection.
A lot of the phones now they come in actually built with a feature that allows you to create an access
point and share the connection that you have on your 3G through Wi-Fi so you can connect your phone
from another phone or from a laptop.
Now when you actually do this your phone is the server and your phone is the router for example which
means that all the packets that's sent from any device connected to your IP will be sent to your phone
cause your phone will actually go and get that request and give it back to the client.
So you actually don't need to do anything to become the man in the middle.
You're already the man in the middle when you create an access point on your phone.
So the simplest way to do this is literally just use the feature that comes with your phone.
Create a hotspot and then you can use any of the methods that we did with WSP attacks so you can start
the shark and start sniffing.
Or you can start doing DNS spoofing.
You can do this also if you can do all the attacks.
You can even do the scenarios that we talked about and we will talk about that apply to you when you
are the man in the middle.
The only thing is that just make sure you actually use your wireless card when you start sniffing or
when you want to do DNS spoof.
So make sure you actually choose lines you're also is your wireless card.
I'll show you how you can see that.
You can see that from your menu.
So here if I go on my column and you you can see that my wireless card here.
It's called 9:0.
So that's the one that you'd want to use when you're sniffing.
I'll show you another way of checking your wireless card so if you go on terminal you Quraan Erewhon
Enghien and it's a list your cards
and as you can see here my 9:0 is my wireless card.
So that's the one you'd be using when you're sniffing So using your hotspot so create an hotspots form
settings and sniffing it.
Use an DNS spoof and they are peaceful.
Sorry using DNS spoof and SSL strip and T-Sharon like we did with WSP.
You can't do that or you can use Zanti right here and from Zanti if you click on the Zanti menu and
you go on these other.
Now this will show you a menu that is actually very similar to the man in the middle menu that we saw.
So this man is actually very simple.
The only difference is that when you click on the on it's going to create an access point and you can
enable SSL strip.
You can do DNS spoofing.
You can replace images capture downloads replace downloads.
We explained all these with the people reasoning future of Zanti so I'm not going to explain them again
because it is very similar.
It's literally the same.
So you go on the settings and then you can enable it by tapping on the on or off.
You can also see the log requests by clicking on The View and we see how we can use that as well.
The logged images and all that.
We had a look on it with the man in the middle.
The only problem with Zanti is that an NDA allows you to share your 3G connection.
So I fear if you're using a tablet that doesn't have 3G like mine or if you just don't have 3G connection
you will not be able to use Zanti because you basically tethers your 3G connection to your wife.
Exactly like what happens when you go through settings and you create a hotspot.
Now what I'm going to be showing you in future videos is if you use a tool called Man or tool kit my
whole kit is very cool because it allows you to use two wireless cards if you want.
So you can use 3G.
But I'm actually going to be using it with two wireless cards for the reason that if you have a 3G you
can use Zanti and it's much easier and much simpler.
But if you have two wireless cards and you want to use Mahna then we'll see how well you can use that
and you can basically create fake access point or a hotspot which people can connect to.
They'll have internet access and whenever they log in to any web so you'll be able to get their log
is the usernames and passwords should be able to do DNS spoofing and all that cool stuff because you're
the man in the middle.
So again I've said that in previous videos when I say you're the man in the middle you can replace the
attacks you can mix the attacks if you have an idea of a different attack.
You can do it as long as the packets are flowing through your device.
The method is not important.
So as long as you are the man in the middle all these attacks that I'm going to explain and this section
you can apply them to ARPU poisoning for example or you can apply them to the body USP attack.
So the method of becoming the man in the middle is not important as long as you are the man in the middle.
You can run these attacks.