Right.
So from the previous video we know that if we want to share the 3G connection on our phone or on our
tablet we can simply just create a hotspot using the default settings all that comes in with Android
and then we can sniff data or read them modify them the same way that we did with the bad we attack
so we can use T-Sharon we can use DNS spoof we can use SSL strip all that kind of stuff we can do the
scenarios that we did straight after we create that hotspot so people are going to connect to the hotspot.
Yeah you'll be automatically be the man in the middle because people connected to your own hotspot and
they will send their requests to your computer because you are the server or to your device and you
will be sending them the replies.
You could also do the same thing.
Share your 3G connection and create a hotspot using your wife ID card using Zanti.
The nice thing about Zanti it has a graphical interface so you can enable a small strip reading passwords
usernames.
Basically do the same stuff that you can do manually but much easier using the graphical user interface.
Again using it using the other.
And then the interface is very similar to the interface that we used when we were doing HRP poisoning
with Zanti.
That's why I didn't go over it because it's very simple.
What I want to go over though is doing the same thing but using a different tool which is called Nat
tool kit.
Now I know it exists on laptops and on Android devices so you can use it on both.
It works on Linux operating systems and it's used the exact same way both on Android and on your Linux
system so if you learn how to use it with Android you'll be able to use it on your laptop.
My tool kit will allow you to create an access point and evil access point.
The cool thing about it is that we will be able to use two wireless cards instead of using the Internet
on 3G.
So we're going to use the Internet connection on one wireless card and we're going to use the second
wireless card as to broadcast the signal of the router so we will not need 3G for this attack.
Now I'm going to use as I said two wireless cards one of them is the internal one and the second one
will be an external wireless card the external one I'll be connect in it using an RTG cable and RTG
cable is basically just a cable that allows you to connect you SB devices to your Android device.
I'll show you what it looks like.
It's very cheap you can get it for around seven to 10 years.
So around $12.
So just what it looks like so that's what it looks like.
This is a the RTG cable which allows you to charge your phone while connecting it to a wireless card.
Some phones you actually have to use a Y UTG cable because the battery on the device does not support
or it's not enough to run your external wireless device.
So I'm actually using a white cable
so my that comes in with three scripts that allow you to run an evil access point.
The first one is the simplest one which is a start no upstream will basically give you an access point
with no internet connection.
So once you run this attack you'll see an access point.
People can connect to it but it will not have an internet connection.
And instead it's going to run your web server that you have a local web server that you have on your
device and you can do DNS spoofing or you can do other stuff to get users to enter usernames or passwords
but there will be no Internet connection on that network.
These are not simple is my favorite one which basically starts a wireless access point with internet
connection.
So when clients connect to that wireless network they will have internet connection and because you
are the server all the packets will be coming to you and going back naturally without having to do anything
because they will send it to you voluntarily.
So once you do that you can do SSL strip you can start the sheriff you can do DNS spoof you can do these
scenarios because you will be the man in the middle.
The third one which is start now its fall will start your access point with internet connection.
It will also start a few tools like SSL strip SSL split fire fireline which sniffs cookies and it will
also attempt to bypass haziest Yes.
Now personally I prefer running.
The simple one and then run in any attacks that I want manually because if any of these attacks does
not work properly I can see what's going wrong and I can fix it.
You can also run man I took it from the Kalli menu.
I don't like to do that though because again when you run it from the calumny there is only a start
button.
So you don't really know if it's actually running or if you have something went wrong whereas when you
run it from the terminal you can see all of the logs all the messages.
And you can see if something went wrong you can see what it is you can debug it and fix it.
So in the next videos we'll see how we can run our evil access point connect to it check if it has internet
connection and see how we can sniff data and modify it or do all the cool stuff that we do when we are
the man in the middle.