OK.
So before I actually start using mine i kids I'd like to show you the wireless interfaces that I have
installed on my device.
So right now I only have my internal device or my internal wireless card.
And as you can see it's connected to a network called to you to I'm going to launch the terminal and
just confirm that for you.
So the command that you use to see your wireless cards is either config
and as you can see that I have land zero wireless card here that's my internal one and it's associated
with a network called TV2 So yes ID is the name of the network and it's too wide too.
So this will be used as the card that will provide the internet connection and I'll use my external
wireless card to broadcast the signal of the network.
So the external wireless card is a U.S. card and I'm going to connect and use an RTG cable that I showed
you on it looks like in the previous video.
So I'm going to connect my external cowd physically and then I'm going to give it two seconds and I'm
going to run I w config to see if the card has been recognized.
I'm going to and as you can see now we have a card called 9 1 and it's not connected to any network
right now.
So this is perfect.
Now I'm going to go back to my launcher menu and show you the settings that you can do for the mana
to.
So the first option is the interface and I could hear LAN because this is the external the name of the
external wireless card.
And this is what we are going to use to broadcast the signal.
The VSS idea here this is the MAC address of the network.
You can put any mac address that you want.
The SS ID is the name of the network that will be broadcasted.
So I'm calling for the Internet to attract people to connect to that network.
And then when they connect I'll naturally be the man in the middle and I can do any man in the middle
that I like to use in T-shirt.
As a sales rep do any of the scenarios that we did DNS pooping whatever that I want the channel is the
channel that is going to be used to broadcast the signal.
And these last two options are for karma.
Karma is an option that allows you to make a network or an access point that is identical to an existing
access point.
The reason why you do this is you can create an access point identical to an access point that uses
an encryption or a key and then trigger the users to connect to your fake access point and then ask
them to enter the user name who's in a web page so the users have to be socially engineered and you
have to kind of convince them to enter their username and password in a web site for their Wi-Fi network.
And then you'll have the username and password for the wife and that's all.
Now we're not going to be doing this in this video because we're all we want to do is just create an
access point with internet connection get people to connect to it.
And then we will get them on in the middle so we can do any of them on in the middle attacks that we
know so I'm going to leave these to us zero.
And the other thing that I want to show you here in the settings.
I'm going to go to the not mine simple which is the one that we're going to use.
So it's access point with internet connection only and it's not going to do any of the man in the middle
attacks we're going to have to do them manually.
The most important thing is just make sure that you have your upstream as the wireless card that is
connected to the Internet.
So I showed you before how landgrab was associated with the network called y2.
So this is my interface that is connected to the Internet in the upstream and then in the future I have
a line one which is my interface that will be used to broadcast the signal.
I've also removed all the comments here.
You usually see hash tags before all of these commands because when you remove them then you'll be able
to turn off the wireless network by type in return.
So that's it.
Now I just want to show you the things that I had.
The first thing that I'm going to do before I start my access point is make sure that my IP tables is
clear and it does not contain any rules that might draw packets and prevent the access point from working
properly.
So we did this when we did divide us we attack as well to allow the packets to flow freely through our
device and we use the scripts that I had in my resources which is called flush IP tables.
So I'm just going to use the exact same script right now.
So it's Bysshe I have it started.
And as the card piles flush IP tables.
SH And because you don't see any error messages that means the command was run successfully.
So the next thing we're going to do is run our evil access point.
So first I'm going to navigate to we're not Mahna is installed which is in us or share
Mannat toolkit
and we're on mana.
So I'm basically just using CD to navigate or to change the working directory to that working directory
where the run scripts for Mom Mannah are stored.
And I'm just going to do an ls to show you all the transcripts that you can use.
So Elyse will just list the files that are in that directory.
And as you can see that we have a file for each option that I explained in the previous video.
So file for the fall for the simple and for the no upstream and each one of them has a kit kat and a
lollipop version.
So the Kit-Kat is for Android for point four point four and a lollipop is for Android 5 and you can
also see that we have the option that I didn't explain it's to run back to our factory on the access
point.
We will run.
Now I'm not going to use that right now and I'm going to explain this in future videos.
So for now we're just going to ignore it.
Now I'm only going to run the simple nuts which will create a network that has internet connection people
can connect to it access the Internet and then I can do all the attacks manually like we did before
so we can do DNS spoofing SSL of all that.
As I said before the same way that we did them with the bad U.S. attack.
So I'm going on the bash start mana or sorry start not simple
Kit-Kat because I have androids point four point four.
SH I'm going to return and I'm going to give it some time to start the access point.
Now the access point is running.
And as you can see it says hit enter to kill me or to stop the access point.
OK so everything is done now.
The attack is running and the network should be broadcasting.
So now you have an Internet network and it's sharing the wireless connection is sharing the internet
connection on one of my wireless cards which is called Gannes you know and it's broadcast in it through
another wireless card connected using the RTG cable which is called Leinwand and when people connect
to this network they will have internet connection and we will naturally be the one in the middle because
we are the servers so they have to send the packets to us and we will be sending the responses.
Therefore we carry these packets modify them and do all the attacks that we learned and we will learn
when you are the man in the middle.
So lets just check and see if the network if we can see the network.
And as you can see here we have a network called the internet.
I'm not going to connect to it now because that will disconnect while you're mirroring here for the
Android device.
So I'm going to connect to it from a Windows device in the next video and we'll see what we can do.
And we'll check if it has internet connection or not.