OK so here I'm on my Windows machine.
I'm going to look for my network see if it exists connect to it check if it has internet connection
and then we'll see how we can run all the attacks that we learned before in order to sniff packets modify
them read them do all that cool stuff.
So as you can see here is my network.
It's called the Internet and I'm going to click on connect to connect to the network
and as you can see I was able to successfully connect to the network.
So let's check if we actually have internet connection.
I'm just going to do a ping on Google com
and as you can see we're getting responses from Google which means that the network is fully connected
to the Internet.
OK so I'm just going to open my browser and go on being dot.com and as you can see that I have Internet
connection here.
Now we are the man in the middle as I said in the previous video so we can do all the attacks the same
way that we did them with about us be attacked so you can use the shark you can use as a cell strap
you can use DNS if you can do the scenarios that we did with DARPA poisoning and with the body to we
so as long as you are the man in the middle.
You can do the exact same attacks that we did when you are the one in the middle.
You can mix and match these attacks.
It doesn't matter as long as the packets flow through your device.
So I'm going to sniff packets just to show you which interface to use and how they can figure out which
configuration you should use.
So I'm just going to open up a new terminal window
and I'm going to use T-shirts like we used before.
This time I'm going to set the interface to one so sorry you need to space here so remember with the
bad us we attack we say to our.
And the zero because that was the interface where the packets were coming or flowing through.
Now we're going to use land one for the reason that Leinwand is the interface that is broadcast in the
signal.
So it's the same interface that we have it in the configuration here in the manual configuration.
So I have one here to broadcast the signal and I have it in the simple as well as the PH y interface.
So that's the one that you want to sniff on.
Not the one that has the internet connection so none is the one that has internet connection.
I'm going to sniff on line one which is the one that is broadcasting the signal and then we're just
going to put everything else the same.
So I just wanted to show you are.
And that you know that the interface that you should use one is anything when doing all these attacks
is 9:1 which is the one that you are using to broadcast the signal.
So let's call this evil a pee cup
going to enter
and now it's capture in packets on one.
And let's just go ahead now again I said you can use the cells as the cell strip and all that.
But we've already explained how to use that and it'll be a waste of time to do it again.
It's the exact same way that you use it when the body has be attacked with the difference that you change
the interface to the interface that is broadcast and the signal.
So I'm just going to go on my free sites my generator and plug in with my username and password just
to show you that this actually works and all the packets are flowing.
You can actually see here that the number of packets increase straight away when I'm browsing the internet.
So we're going to go test evil AP come up with user 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 6 password then.
Now it's wrong what it should should have been logged in here.
So I'm going to control and see this and then open it and wireshark the same way that we did before
with our bad US attack.
OK so I downloaded or I shared my tap file here with my device and I'm going to open it using wireshark
like we did before.
So I'm going to go and file open my downloads and I have it here.
Evil A kept us up and opened that and I'm going to certain info and firster hasty TV exactly like we
did with the U.S. we attack and I'm going to look for upholster costs.
And we can see that we have the post request.
Here we go on the line.
And as you can see I'm going to double click it actually to show it to you better as you can see that
I have my user name is just as evil IP dot com and the password is 1 2 3 4 5 6 7.
So exactly this is this is exactly what we did with the bad USP.
It's just to show you that you need to use LAN one or the interface that is broadcast in as the one
that you want to sniff on.
Then you can do all the attacks that we did before you can do the scenarios you can do as a striptease
shark DNS spoof still cookies anything that we did before and use the tools that you can use when you
are the man in the middle.
You can use them because when you do when you create an evil access point you will be the man in the
middle naturally so the users or the clients will send will interact with you as the router because
you are there either so they will send you all the requests they want and you will be sending them all
the responses that they should get.