Now throughout the course we're going to be using a number of penetration testing tools.
You can go ahead and install each of these tools manually or you can do what most protesters do including
myself and save time and effort and use an operating system designed for Hocken.
We're going to be using an operating system called Kalli Linux and it's just a flavor of Linux based
on Debian and it comes in with all the programs and the applications that we need to use pre-installed
and pre-configured.
This means that we can just install this operating system and then start learning our Hocking.
There are two options to install Kallie.
You can install it as a virtual machine inside your current operating system or you can install it as
a main machine as a main operating system.
Throughout the course I'm actually going to be using it as a virtual machine because using it as a virtual
machine works exactly the same as installing it as a mean machine because it will be completely isolated
from your computer because it's only going to run inside virtual box.
So if you break it or if you mess things up it's very very easy to fix.
It's very easy to go back to other snapshots other configurations and also you won't lose any functionality
by using it as a virtual machine.
That's why I always use it as a virtual machine.
In this lecture I'm going to cover how to install it as a virtual machine inside virtual box.
Now I'm going to be doing the steps on the Mac OS X computer but these tapes are exactly the same regardless
of what operating system you use.
So if you're on Windows or on Linux you just have to download the Virtual Box version of your computer
and then the steps shown in this lecture are exactly the same after installing Virtual Box going include
the download link in the resources of this lecture.
I have it already opened in here.
All you have to do is just scroll down.
Make sure you click on the calendar next virtual box images not on the VM where and then download the
version of Cali's that's compatible with your system.
So if you have a 64 bit computer download the 64 bits.
If the if you have the 32 bits download the 32 bits now one click on this will start to download for
you.
If you're using Internet Explorer or edge browser then you're going to have to right click and save
target as on Chrome and Firefox you can just click the link.
Now this is downloading for me and I'm going to stop it because I've already downloaded so I already
have it downloaded in here.
And as you can see you should get a file with a dot over the extension so you have the name followed
by dot or a in here.
So to solve this in a virtual box all you have to do is literally just double click the file and as
you can see I get a window which will allow me to import this virtual machine.
Now I'm going to keep everything the same for now and I'm just going to click on import.
Now that said the virtual machine is ready to be used now before I started I want to show you how to
modify some of its settings so I'm going to click on it.
Then we're going to click on the settings in here and the first thing that I'm going to do.
I'm going to go to System and I'm going to modify the amount of RAM it has now dependent on how much
total RAM you have on your computer.
You can leave this at 2 if you want but one gigabyte is enough for Cadie.
I usually leave it to because I have 16 gigs of RAM but if you have less 1 gigabyte is enough for it.
Also a few come here on the processors.
You'll see that by default I have two processors assigned to it.
Again I have 8 per use.
So two is not going to cause too much pressure on my computer.
If you have less.
Once is enough for Kalli.
Now we're going to go to the network settings and we're going to set this to use and not network.
Now sometimes when you set this to another network you won't see a network name in here.
If you don't please check out my link in the resources and it will show you how to create and not network.
For me it already has a network so I'm going to keep it on this one and what the setting basically does
is it's going to create a virtual network where my host machine which is my Mac OS X computer in here
is going to be the router for this network and then all the virtual machines are going to be clients
connected to this network.
So they're going to get Internet connection from my host machine and at the same time all of my virtual
machines will be connected to a virtual network.
This is very handy because my virtual machines will be able to communicate with each other.
We can use one of them to hack into the other.
We can use it to test networks attacks and much more so it'll first allow my virtual machines to have
Internet connection.
It also allow them to communicate with each other and it'll do all of this through a virtual network.
It will not use any of your wireless adapters or any of your wireless cards.
It will create a virtual Internet network.
So as far as the virtual machine is concerned they're going to think that they're connected to a network
through a wire so that's it I'm done with my settings right now and I'm going to click on OK.
And we can start our virtual machine now to start it.
All we have to do is just click on the start button in here.
Now I'm going to click inside the virtual machine and hit enter.
And we are inside the virtual machine.
Now it's asking us for the username and the default user name is root.
So our O.T. and then asking us for the password and the default password is the reverse of that which
is t o r
and that's it.
Now I'm inside my virtual machine now since we installed this using the ready image.
We can just click on this on the green button here or we can go to View full screen and we'll be able
to go in full screen and the screen will resize automatically to the size of our screen.
Now note in here you should actually see a network icon because we set this machine to use that network.
Since we don't have a network icon This means that this machine didn't get connected to the Nat network.
So if I open my browser in here you'll see that it's not connected to the Internet to fix this issue.
We're just going to go all the way to the top.
This is going to display our menus.
We're going to go to devices network and we're going to click on Connect network adapter.
You only have to do this once and then the virtual machine will automatically connect to the network.
Now once you do this if you give it a few seconds you'll see that I have a network icon appearing in
here.
And if I click it you'll see it looks like I'm connected to a wired network.
As you can see in here it says wired connected.
So Cali thinks it's connected to a wired network.
Now if I just click try again in my browser you'll see that I have internet access so that's it.
That shows how to install Callanan acts as a virtual machine.
Don't be intimidated by this new operating system.
We're going to go through the basics and we're going to use it a lot and it's actually going to become
very easy for you to use.
Also like I said you won't lose any functionality when you install Linux as a virtual machine.
It's actually better to install it as a virtual machine because it's completely isolated from your computer
and it'll be very easy to fix if things go wrong.
Keep in mind installing this on different hardware and different computers might show you some errors
on some issues.
So please if you have any errors just add them in the discussions and I'll help you resolve them.