So now we're going to talk about information gathering information gathering is one of the most important
steps in penetration testing.
For example say if you're trying to gain access to a computer that exists on a certain network first
of all you want to be able to gather as much information as possible about that network so that you
can connect to it whether it uses encryption.
How far the network is what kind of security is being used on that network.
The IP address the MAC address all that kind of stuff about the network once you can actually connect
to the network you want to be able to gather information about the devices that exist on this network.
Once you gather information about these devices you want to see which one of them is your target once
you locate your target you want to be able to know what IP address it is.
What operating system neurons doesn't run Windows does or on Linux.
Is it a phone.
If it's a Windows version of Windows.
If you get the version you want to see once you know the version you might be able to look for buffer
overflow exploits and think in full access to that laptop.
That's just an example.
So information gathering is very important the more information that you gather the more likely that
you will be able to gain access to your target and achieve your goal.
So today or in this lecture we're going to talk about network discovery or what's known as wardriving
now basically wardriving is where you have your device and you'd be walking or driving around the area
that you think that your target is and or the network is in and gather information about these networks.
So we're going to use an app called Wi-Fi analyzer which gives us information about old Wi-Fi networks
or are around us.
So it gives us information about the network name gives us information about the MAC address the channel
the encryption the speed the signal strength and it even shows us the devices that each network or the
devices that are connected to our current network.
We'll talk about that in the next class.
So I'm just going to go to my calculator next device right here and you can download this app from the
App Store.
So as you can see here I have it right here.
Wi-Fi analyzer.
So I'm just going to tap it
and as you can see straight away it's showing me the networks that are around me and we can see that
there are four networks and two or two has the strongest signal.
That's because this is the one that actually connected to right now.
And then you can see the rest is fluctuating because there actually none of them is my network.
The other one is blue.
It's not very well visible.
This is one of my networks as well.
That's what it is.
It's a bit strong.
So this curve basically shows you the signal strength of all the networks around you
so I'm going to tap on the view here on top and I'm going to go to the time graph
this will basically show you the signal strength across time.
And as you can see it's moving.
So you can see which networks are consistent and which networks aren't on top.
You can filter networks by clicking on the network name on top.
So for example if I click on horizon right there
it's going to highlight it for me.
So if you click on UPC you 4 1 1 1 9 you can see it's highlighted there for me so you can have a better
look at it.
So I'm going to look for my network which is to you y2 and I'm highlighting it right there and you can
see it is the one with the strongest signal and the most consistent of all of them.
Now the other view that we have is the channel rating and it'll basically show you which channels are
being used most.
Now this is actually really handy because if you go back I'm just going to go back to the channel graph
right here.
You can see that my network is both of my networks actually to Aitu and the UPC 1:54 are both on the
same channel but they are not used in any of the channels that are used by other networks.
By doing this I can actually avoid overlapping.
And I'll have a stronger signal in my house for my networks.
Now I have them both run on the same channel because the y2 is just experimental or a temporary network
that I only use when I'm making videos.
So usually I don't use both.
I'd use one or the other.
So that's why I have them on the same channel.
But a good tip for you if there is a lot of networks running on the same channel around your area then
it's a good idea to change the channel of your network to another channel.
So I'm going to go now to the AP list and this will basically give you a really comprehensive and good
look of all the network so it'll show you the MAC address here on top as you can see.
So that's the physical address of each network.
This doesn't change and it always stays the same
and also shows you the channel it shows you the speed and it shows you the encryption or the security
you so you can see this network my network uses WPA if ask yes.
OK.
If you go down you'll see actually all of them are using WPA at the moment.
You can also see your current address because I'm actually connected to this network so you can see
my current IP address here.
And the last one which is one of the really nice features that I like about this app is the signal meter.
Now this is really handy because it shows you how strong is the signal of the network that you pick.
So from here if you tap on this you can pick any network strong networks around.
So I'm going to pick to you to for example and we can see that the signal is full so it's perfect.
Now if you start moving around the signal is going to change so it's really good say if you're in a
place and then you're trying to see what is the part that has the best coverage or the strongest signal
in that place.
Then you can basically just pick the network that you want and start walking around or moving around
until you find the area where the strongest signal.
Now this comes in really really handy when you're trying to break into kids whether it's WPA or WAPT
is you usually want as part with a really good signal
even if you're using your laptop in order to do that.
It's really handy to use your phone or your tablet and start moving around to find the place with the
strongest signal and then put your laptop there or put your wife I card there and start trying to break
into that network.
We will talk about break in kids whether it's the blue WPA or WPA to and stronger or in the future lectures.
But I just would like to point that this will come in really really handy when you're trying to do this
and you'll see it in the future when you actually try to do some tests.
It's really difficult to get.
Or it's really important to get a place with a good signal.
And this will help you to do that.
And it's going to be really really useful.