After doing wardriving and targeted a certain network in many cases our target would not be open so
the network would be using a certain type of encryption whether it's WPP WPA or WPA too.
Now there are a number of methods to crack each type of encryption before you can do that.
There is a number of concepts that you have to learn about networks and how they work and how each one
of these encryptions work and communicate with the devices that are connected to it.
I actually have a full course explaining how to crack network Keys starting from scratch talking about
these concepts about money or mode and MAC address all these things how they communicate with each other.
And then I explain a practical attacks against each one of these incorruption so against WEP or WPA
to the cracking method is exactly the same whether you do it from a Linux device or whether you do it
from your net or because you'd be using the exact same tools which are aircraft ngi and reversed.
So when you're going to be cracking and you will be running exactly the same commands whether you're
doing it from a laptop or if you're doing it from your Android device.
Therefore I kind of thought if I explained it from to do how to do it from Android device it would be
going kind off topic because it's not really something special about Android devices.
It's not a special attack that is made for Android devices.
And also I'd be repeating myself.
So if you're interested in to learn how to do that then have a look on my course on this link.
And I'll also put it in the air resources if you like it.
I'll give you 10 I'll give it to you for only $10 because you're already about one of my courses so
I'm not going to charge you for the next one.
I'm not going to charge you a lot for the next one.
So it's a full course it has about I think 25 video starting from scratch to all the powerful methods
that you can use to crack these interruptions.
In order to do this from your Android device Unfortunately the Wi-Fi card inside Android devices is
not very powerful so you need a Wi-Fi card that supports injection and supports monitor mode.
So an example is the alpha a USA 6.
It's very cheap and powerful and you can use it to do that in order to connect it to your tab and to
your tablet or to your phone.
You're going to need an OT G Y cable.
So he actually won an RTG by cable looks like.
So that's what it looks like it has basically connect to your USP.
Here so you can that you can you don't have to connect the wireless card you can connect anything that
connects using USV to this part.
Then you connect this part to your phone and you connect this to your cable to charge the phone so the
phone will be charge and at the same time you will need this when you're using the Wi-Fi when you're
using a wife ID card because it takes a lot of power and the battery inside some of these mobile devices
cannot support it.
So that's why we save just get a white cable and get non-fact card and I'll show you how you connect
it to your Android device.
So that's because that's the only difference between computers and Android devices is just Kinect in
your.
Once it's connected.
The attacks are exactly the same.
So get your cable connected as I showed you now two seconds ago in the picture.
I'll actually before we do that launch my terminal and the command that you use to see your wireless
card is really you can think so I'm going to run that and as you can see that I have my wireless card
right here is called
nonzero.
And as you can see it's connected to my network too so I'm going to connect my RTG cable Make sure you
connect your wireless carrier to the RTG cable and then connect it to the power source first then connect
it to your Android device.
So the last step is connecting it to your Android device.
Once you do that I'm going to do either config again
and as you can see that I have my loved one connected right now so that is my wireless card my Alfar
card that supports injection.
So I'll just show you how to do wardriving using this card.
Now you'll see actually we're going to detect so many more networks more than what we did with the internal
one simply because this is a more powerful card.
So I'm going to do Ehrmann Now again all these modes and all these commands are explained in much more
detail in my course about tracking kids.
So everyone ngi basically just the tool that allows you to start to monitor mode on cards again monitor
mode and all these modes are explained in the car so I'm not going to go into detail now so I don't
want and you start I'm going to start with the card which is none one
and now the cards are dead on the line 1 1.
So and then I'm going to do a road dump.
So these commands are exactly the same you run them from your laptop.
So basically if you learn how to do it on your own computer you can do it on Android.
And if you learn how to do it on Android you can do it on computers so heire don't angry.
I'm going to put my wireless card name with weiter mode so it's LAN one 1 and I'm just going to reduce
the font.
Because this is going to produce a lot of output and it's you won't be able to see all of it.
So I'm just going to make the phone smaller
and I'm going to enter
and as you can see it's already getting so much more networks than we were able to get with Wi-Fi and
Lizer.
It's because we're using a more powerful wireless card.
So you can see here you have the MAC address you have the power which is the distance of each of these
A-P is how far it is from you.
This is the beacons which each router sends the amount of data.
So that's the useful packets the time the Janno the speed of each of them the encryption and then the
algorithm that's used in the encryption the authentication type and the network name and also shows
you the devices that are connected to this network if we if we started on a certain network or if we
wait for it for a little bit again all of this is explained in much more detail onto my wife Vikki cracking.
I didn't want to go into detail here again because it's not something special to Android devices and
it didn't want to go off topic.
Also because it's relatively big subject so it will distract you a bit if I start talking about it right
now.
So if you are interested in it send me a message.
I will give you that course for only $10 and then you can do the attacks from your laptop or from your
Android device.