Now we're going to talk about something called network mapping.
So let's say you're connected to a network or you connected to your target network and now you want
to discover all the connected devices to this network so there might be five six or ten devices connected
to this network and you want to gather information about these devices you want to know their IP address
and MAC address their operating system and maybe even the programs that are running on these devices.
All this information will make achieving your target easier.
So if you know what operating system runs you can look for exploits for the operating system.
If you can see for example ports 21 open maybe you'll try to connect to it through FCP and see if there
is an anonymous account.
If not try to see what FGP server is running and look for buffer overflow exploits and maybe try to
exploit them maybe even if you find local exploits you can send something to the target person and way
to gain access to the device.
Well will going to talk about all that later but for now we're just going to see how we can gather information
about these devices see what services they're running and maybe try to gain access to these devices.
So I'm going to show you a few ways or a few apps that you can use to do that.
We're going to start by the simplest and the ones that give you less information but they're quick and
then we're going to go to the more complicated more advanced apps.
So for a start just to get an idea of what network mapping is I'm going to use the same apps that we
used before Wi-Fi analyzer.
So I'm just going to tap on it.
And right now I'm actually connected to my network.
So if we go to the AP list you can see that I'm connected to you Aitu
so I'm going to go here on this three dots right there and I'm going to go on tools.
I'm going to tap on LAN neighbors so this will basically look through all the connected devices and
it'll show me information about these devices.
Now first of all they can actually see some info about the current network so you can see the IP of
the gateway the IP of the gateway basically means the IP of the router or the server of this network.
So this is where whenever any device wants to access something within the network it's going to send
its request here.
So if it wants to access any web site or anything it's going to send that request to this IP.
You can also see the mosque and the network say so this is all the possible IPs that you can find within
the network.
And that's basically the range that specifies the range which is from 1 9 1 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 1 2 1 9 2
1 6 8 1 2 5 4.
If you look up the first one now we know the gateway is 1 9 2 1 6 8 1 1.
So if we look at the first device we can see that this has the same IP.
So that must be our outer or our server for the network and you can see that its KCC so its made by
HTC it was able to detect that.
And then when we look on the other device right here we can see that we have one device connected to
the network and thats 1 9 2 1 6 8 145 and the username is as 00 us.
And that's actually my Linux machine right here.
So I'll just show you that if I open my terminal you can see that the name of my machine is as 00 as.
So I was able to find the name of this machine because it's connected to the same network so I was able
to get that.
It also got me my mac address right here so I'm going to show you that this is correct so if I go become
thick and this is my wireless card ifconfig de-th one
as you can see the MAC address is actually the same.
So it was able to get the MAC address of this device as well.
It was also able to get the manufacturer of my wireless card which is this right here.
Now I'm going to go back and if you go on the or you I look up from the tools they will basically just
tell you the manufacturer of any device used in the MAC address.
Now the device has to be connected to your network.
So I'm just going to do the same it already got this for me so I'm just going to do it just to show
you.
So I'm just going to put the MAC address of my laptop which is zero
8 5 and I can see it I actually got it already right here.
So that's it for now.
Very simple too.
It allows you to discover all the connected device in your network now and the future videos we're going
to be using more advanced tools and we'll see that they'll actually show us much more information than
this to.