So in the previous video we saw how we can map or discover all the connected devices to our network.
We were only able to get very basic information such as their IP address their MAC address and then
the manufacturer of the MAC address.
Now today we're going to use a tool called Zanti 2 which is a mobile penetration testing framework.
It allows us to run a number of attacks and information gathering tasks.
So we're going to be using this tool in different videos.
And today's video we're going to use it to discover all the connected devices and get more information
than the last time.
So we're going to see what kind of information we'll get.
We'll be able to guess.
We will get the MAC address an IP just like last time but we will also be able to get the operating
system the open court and preview in future videos we'll even try to get the programs that are running
on this ports and the version of these programs.
So Zanti is not available on the App Store so you can download this from the following link.
All you have to do is just download it top it and install it.
So make sure you download this link from your mobile device or from your tablet.
Now once you download Zanti it's going to look like this.
So I'm just going to tap on it and I've already run this.
So as you can see discover devices so I'm just going to tap on the refresh sign there.
And I'm not going to use the intrusive scan which looks for vulnerabilities.
I'm just going to leave it the way it is and I'm going to type OK.
And as you can see it's saying that it's mapping the network is trying to discover the connected devices.
OK.
So now as you can see it stopped mapping the devices and we have all the devices that are connected
to the network.
And as you can see the first thing you notice beside each device on this column you see an icon that
represents the operating system or the type of device.
So you can see for the first hour right here you have a router icon which tells you that this is a router
that also was able to get the MAC address and the manufacturer telling us it's a HTC device or the wireless
card or the wireless hardware used in that router is made by HTC if we go on the next one you can see
as well the IP the MAC address and that it is an Android device which is actually this device as you
can see it says on the bottom of this device.
And then the next one it was able to detect that it's a Linux device.
I remember last time it wasn't one we used Wi-Fi analyzer.
It wasn't able to tell us what operating system used devices.
So from here we can actually know that this is a Linux device or something that runs Linux.
We still have the name of the device which is as 00 us and we have the MAC address and the manufacturer.
And the next one we can see that we discovered an Apple device and the name of the device is that 00
said.
And it says an Apple device here as well.
And we have the MAC address.
Another extra thing that you notice is right here which is the ports that are open on each device.
So we can see that if we tap on the router you'll see that it has one port open.
So if we go on the absconds right here on the top right you can see that it has port.
If you open
now and map is actually a command line tool that it's short for network marker and it's the best and
most popular port scanner that is there on the Internet now you can use this on Linux on Windows and
on all operating systems.
It actually comes in installed with Nat hunters so you can run if you know how to use and you can actually
run the commands using the command line in that Hunter and you'll be able to get the results or you
can use Zanti and I'll show you in the next video is how you can actually use and map from within Zanti.
And this is all the information that was able to get but you don't really need to go through this as
it's already shown in the back in the main menu here.
So basically what Zanti does Iran's and my for you.
And then it shows you the results in a really nice and organized way.
So what if you needed to go through the command line you have it by clicking on the maps counts as I
showed you another device so I'm going to show you.
Here is the next device I'm going to tap on it.
The open ports as you can see there here port 80 9 0 2 4 9 1 5.
Now we don't know what's running on this port site even if we come here on the unmap scans and I'm just
going to look for that next device.
So it's one 45 it's IP which is this one.
So if you come here we can actually just see the open port.
As you can see right here we have eighty nine 0 2 and 4 9 1 5 2.
We don't know what what programs are on and on them like we can't see that 1862.
It's usually hasty.
So it's not a big deal like it didn't really tell us more information about it.
So we'd like to know for example what server is not our port what version of that server so we can actually
try and hack that computer through that server or through that port.
Sorry.
So I'll go back and I want to show you something like I mentioned that information gathering is one
of the most important steps in penetration testing.
And I wasn't overexaggerating it because let me show you this so I'm going to go on this suppled device
and this is my own tablet.
It's still broken.
And as you can see we have to force open port number two to number 2 2 and 4 6 2 0 7 8.
Now 1:56 usually corresponds to S-sh.
So I'm going to go down here just to confirm and show you so 59.
And here you are that's the IP of the Apple device.
And as you can see that we have 4:22 22 open and it has hate support.
So it's for us as a S-sh service.
As I say it basically is a server that allows you to remotely run Linux commands on the target device.
So it's usually installed on servers for example if you have a web server online when you buy a web
server or rent a web server they'll give you an S-sh account.
So S-sh by using it a certain username and password it will allow you to remotely log in to your Linux
or Windows or even Marko's machine and run commands on the target machine.
So when you jailbreak your device with Apple you use a name with when you jailbreak it.
The root password is actually set to a l p i n e.
So it's the default password.
Most people don't know that and even the people that know that they don't change it including me.
I actually never change it like I don't have this just to show you now.
So when I just broke my device the password is still as a p i n.
So for example when you're doing a scan and then you see an Apple device with port 22 open it's a good
idea just to try to log in to that port with the password.
A L P I N E.
Now let me just do this quickly and show you how you can do this from your laptop or from your that
Hunter device.
I'm just going to do it from the net Hunter device.
Just because we're doing penetration testing using your mobile phone or using your Android but you can
do it from any device that you want.
So I'm just going to go on the net and turn I'm going to go on home so I'm going to go on the luncher
and I'm going to launch Kelly shell and terminal and all I have to do is S-sh into the target.
So the come on this S-sh username is rude and you put it and then put the IP address of the target.
So the IP address was 1 9 2 6 8 1 2009.
I'm going to hit enter and it's telling me you want to trust target I'm going to say yes and now it's
asking me for the password so I'm going to use the password.
It's a L P and it's going to hit enter.
And as you can see I logged in as root.
So if I go you as you can see that I am rude and if I go if I can think just to show you that I am actually
inside that device doesn't have it configured still I don't have that command installed on my tablet
but it is as you can see that it's rude and it's arduous which is the name of the iPod.
And if I say my eyes you can't say it's telling me that I am rude and I am at the target device.
Basically you're just going to be using Unix commands to navigate through the system and you can do
whatever you want because you are rude.
And as I said it has all probably all privileges on the target machine.
So this is basically like it wasn't an actual hack.
It was just a use of information that we gather so we saw there an Apple device.
Has S-sh open on it.
So it was definitely broken.
And we just tried the default password and we were able to log in and gain basic full access to this
device.
So even if this device had no exploit it had the latest and greatest software and the best security
measurements we only logged in through a service which is allowed on the device used in proper username
and password.