Right.
So in this video we're just going to follow on what we did in the previous video.
We're still using Zanti too and we're still connected to the same network and I have the same devices
connected here to the network.
The only difference is that right now we're going to try and determine the actual programs running on
each port.
So I'm going to go on my Linux device which is this one just because it has the most number of force
and we have three services running on port eighty nine 0 2 and 4 9 1 5 2.
And as I showed you before when we go on the scans here you can see that the ports are open but you
can see what programs are running on these ports.
So let me just show you here.
As you can see here we can see that we have TTP and we have on nine or two that we have ISIS running.
And then we have on 9 1 5 2 that are an unknown service is running.
So as I said what Zanti does it actually use is a very powerful tool called a mob and using that too
it can actually show us or get information about the connected devices.
So we're going to go on the scan option here.
And what this does it basically allows us to run advanced scans on the target device.
So it's only going to rise on the device that we selected and not on the whole network.
Now I'm going to go on the scanner type and as you can see there is a number of scans that you can on.
Now I'm not actually going to be around in all of this askance.
It's very simple to run them you basically just have the scan and it does what discount does.
So there's no point of me just wasting time running each one of them.
I'm going to be around in just a few of them to show you how you can run a scan and what information
you'll be getting from each of these scans.
So you can see that we have a scan and quick detection trace route and regular scan all these scans
will basically show what show us more information that what we originally have right now.
So I'm not going to be around or any of these scans.
They're usually quick.
Those are your basic information like what we have right now.
What I'm going to be running though I'm going to be running an intense gun.
So this will basically show you extra information that what we have from last time it will show you
more information about the open court and the programs that are running on these open ports.
Now as you can see on top of it saying that it's mapping network again now give it it's time and then
we'll see what information we get.
Right so we can see that the manual scans completed as you can see there on top and you can do a scan
you can dismiss and see the log.
So I'm going to click on the log
and this is actually the output that was produced by Unmap.
As you can see the first thing that we were able to detect remember when we were seeing that the port
is 80 so we can see that the port is 80.
It's open.
So we were able to get all that before.
But what we have now is the exact program and version on and go on this program so we can see that we
have Apache hasty TPD to point two point twenty two.
And it's right on your want or so before we only knew that it's Linux.
Now we actually know it's running on Ubuntu.
So it's this is the XYZ virgin of Linux and we know that it's Apache.
The exact version of the program
we can also see the 9 0 2 port that is running on SSL VM where authentication daemon.
If we go on this port for 9 1 5 2 again before we didn't know it was just unknown what it's running.
Now we actually know that it's running media on UPMC.
So this is a media server running and we have the exact version of the server so we can actually go
now and look for exploits or default passwords or stuff like that for this server.
And we can see that it's running on Linux three point to point 0 7 non-generic and that is the kernel
version of the Linux of the operating system that the machine is running.
And then you can see it actually has the mac address and the operating system and all that kind of stuff.
And it also performs a trace route on the device as you can see here and we can see it's only one hop
away because we are on the same network.
Right so other showed you there's a number of scans you can pick any scan you want to experiment with
them and each one of them will give you maybe more information than another one.
So and math is a huge tool like there is for courses the only talk about and map.
So if you're really interested into penetration testing I'd highly recommend that you go and learn more
about and map.
As I said you can learn.
You can run and map commands from the terminal straightaway using the Kelly terminal right here.
Or you can just use Zanti which basically run and map commands for you and show them to you in an easy
and nice way.