We saw previously how we can connect our Android device to our target computer and have a tool that
computer that my device is a keyboard then execute certain commands to the username and password then
connect using Remote Desktop.
Then we show the power supply option where we actually inject and we test ploys payload and then have
a reverse interpretor connection which allows us to do a lot of cool stuff on the target machine basically
gives us full access to the target machine.
Today we're going to have a look on another flavor of the A.H. ID keyboard attack.
And this is the Dulcie's.
First of all the rubber ducky is a USP device that you connect to a computer and when you connect it
it runs certain commands exactly the same way that we do it when we connect our Android device.
So it's very similar to the idea keyboard attack.
The difference is there are a lot of DocI scripts out there that are already made.
So you can copy and paste them and use them straight away.
And also you can write your own Docky scripts.
So I'm going to put links for the payload generators for already existing payloads and for resources
on teaching you how to write your own Docky scripts on the resources.
It's actually really simple writing scripts right.
We're going to have a look on them and the next video so you can use existing Dulcie's scripts.
Or you can write your own Dulcie's script or you can use the payload generator.
So let me show you here.
So that's the script Web site.
The script tool kit so you can use the payload generator here on our Web site Alibhai going on create
payload and then you can just basically take what you want to do so you can do information gathering
here such as doing a port scan just computer information user information use the information all that
kind of stuff.
And here you can either use or you can enable the remote desktop you can delete the windows updates
you can get a reverse shell here create a reverse show so you can do all that stuff but we've already
done this we've already made a user and added it to the user who's in Cali and we already made the power
supply and got reverse connection.
So all the cool stuff in the payload We've actually already done them.
So I'm not going to do that I'm going to do something now.
And the next video you can also go on the help here.
And then we can go onto the syntax guide and that will basically show you how you can write the scripts.
So for example if you right you are then that means it's going to show you the windows run box where
you can run ACMD or put something.
So for example here it's poisonous ring TMD and it's running CMG and then they're going to get the command
prompt and then you could run.
Come on.
Come on from.
So it's exactly like the keyboards.
Thank you.
Your device will be pretending that it is a keyboard but you have more flexibility and you have more
options more things that you can do.
Also the keyboard that works on Linux and OSS systems and we saw that the net Hunter doesn't give us
autem doesn't allow us to do a lot of things automatically with them.
So using the rubber ducky you can actually write your own script for us x or for Linux and just write
the command that you want to run on the target machine.
So you have here are a few examples and also show you how you can write your own script now and the
next video I'll show you at Download an execute script which allows us to download a certain file and
executed on the target machine simply by connecting our Android device.