So now we're going to see how we're going to use a script that will download any files from a certain
you or L and execute that file.
Why do I like this script now.
This is because it's actually a really really simple script it's only two lines well two lines to be
executed taking because you can create any you can download any files so you can create any file you
use in any Fromer that you want.
You can create any backdoor any kind of factor that you like you can use a virus you can use trojan
or you can use a key logger you can just use a normal.
You can basically use any file that you want and then you will execute that file.
And if you don't you can just remove the line that executes the file and then you can just get it to
download the file to the target machine.
So this will happen simply by connecting your Android device to the target machine using you speed.
You will download a certain file and execute it.
So first of all let's see what is the script I'm going to be using that will do that.
So the first line is just a delay so it's going to wait for two seconds before it does anything.
Then the second line right here is going to show the Run box.
The third line is the DNA of a 100 milliseconds just to wait until the ront box shows up.
Once we have the run we're going to type in a power shell command which will basically download a file
that is stored on this you're out.
So this is just an IP address of a of a machine that's running a web server on my network.
So this can be anywhere else where your file is stored.
So I basically have a file called not be on this candy machine right here.
So this candy machine if I go to my bar would be WW I have a file called that we see which is basically
just a backdoor created using Val evasion as we saw in the previous video.
So I just have that file.
There's nothing special about it just the back door.
It's stored and this is the IP address of that machine and it's the file is called not Windows XP.
So it's going to download this file is going to rename it to be the ATX either.
So you can replace this with anywhere else that you want and has to be a direct download.
You are.
For where your file is stored.
So it's going to rename it to redirect the XP then it's going to wait for half a second.
It's going to execute the Run box again.
It's going to wait for 100 milliseconds and then it's going to run this.
So if you don't want to run it you can just remove this last line right here and it's just not going
to run it.
And if you want to change the name where it's stored you can change it here.
So for example if you're downloading something does not need you for example if it was a zip then you
just typed dot zip here.
So you're going to have to change the R L for where you are going to save your ex or your file to be
downloaded and you would change this if you want.
This will just run the file.
So if you don't want the file to be Iran you wouldn't change this and make sure that we got the axes
the same here.
So if you rename it here you have to rename it.
So that's the file I'm going to use be using.
And I've already copied it.
So I'm just going to go back to my kind of menu I'm going to go to my page ID the script tag and you
just paste your file here so your paste the rubber duckies script right here.
And then you can click on convert.
So I'm going to click on updates already updated.
Then I'm going to click on convert and that will basically convert it to Haiti.
Id a keyboard attack format so you can see in the preview here that's what how what it looks like when
it's converted.
And I'm just going to go back to my Kaleem and you and I have my listeners here already like as I showed
you in my previous video so I'm just going to do an exploit on it.
And now I was listening.
So I'm going to come here.
I'm basically just going to type on these three little dots and execute the attack.
And we go to our windows.
And as you can see now the attack is actually the command is being written automatically.
So I'm not writing anything.
And that's what I like about it's only two commands.
This this is the first command to download the file and then the second command to run it.
And that's it.
We have them there for their show right here.
So that's why it's really cool that's why I like doing this particular script because it's weather like
there are scripts that will basically give you a reverse show but they need to run more commands.
With this it's actually just really quick to commands and the speed of the command being tied depends
on your processor.
Now my I'm using the 2012 Nexus 7 so it's a bit slow and I have a lot of things running on it in order
to mirror the image and all that.
So for you it might be a lot quicker than what happened to me.
There's one more thing that I want to show you.
And that is already made payloads that you can use with the rubber ducky I didn't I didn't show you
in the previous video so I'm not going to put all this in the resources so I'm just going to show you
here of the payloads that you can get.
So that's all the payload that you can get.
So there's a lot of payloads I can give you you can get a basic terminal command and you want to add
there is always x payload.
There are payloads to allow you to download stuff those Speedos to allow you to upload stuff.
All you have to do is click on the payload right click it copied and pasted in taunter convert and execute.
Same way I just did that.
And the payload I just used I'm going to put it in resources for you to download and to use and test
it on your own machines.