So as I said before the keyboard that works on all operating systems including Windows OS X and Linux.
So by plug in our Android device to an OS X system we can still fool that system that our Android device
is a keyboard and we can still send keystrokes to the system as if we are a keyboard.
So and this video will see how we can use the ID rubber ducky script attacks to create a script that
will use OS X shell and try to connect back to my Android device which will give me full access to that
operating system or to that device.
So basically what we're going to do is we're going to launch terminal.
We're going to run a command to connect to a certain IP and this IP can be any device so it can be Linux.
Another Linux device it can be a Windows device it can be your next punter.
All you need is a tool called netcat to listen on a port.
So before we saw when we were using Mutazz ploys payloads we were using we just ploy to listen for incoming
connections.
Today we're only using a normal connection and normal TCAP connection from us X to another IP.
So you just need a simple to call that Guert which is available on all operating systems and it's preinstalled
on your net punter and on normal Kalli for PCs.
So you can straightaway just run the command and it's going to work.
So let me first show you what the script is like.
It's actually a really really simple.
So I have it here downloaded and I'm going to obviously include it's for you and the resources.
So this is all those.
First of all it does a delay for 1000 and waits for one second.
Then it says Type seen GeoEye and space which basically shows the spotlight for OS X operating system.
So if I type in cmd and space I get my Spotlight search which allows me to run any program just like
when you type in the CND or when you type in the Windows key on Windows machines
then it's going to type in terminal to show the terminal.
Then it's going to wait for 500 for half a second.
Then it's going to type and enter so that will start the terminal for me.
Once it starts the terminal it's going to run this command.
So this is the command that will do the connection.
So all you need to do is modify this part.
This IP address and put the IP address for the device which will receive the connection.
So this should be the device is the same thing when we were using L host so it should be the IP of the
device that will run netcat on it.
And this video I'm not going to be using my Linux some previous videos I was actually use in my Linux
to or.
But today I'm going to run this on or not around that out just to receive the connections.
Today I'm going to do it on my calendar on turtles and that's cuds really simple there's no point of
having two operating systems running on the same time.
So I'm just going to go on my terminal and start netcat which will wait for the connection then we can
execute this attack before I execute this attack.
Though I want to modify this and put my IP address because this IP is wrong so I'm going to just go
see what is my IP address.
You can do that in my home right here.
So you can see that my IP address is 1 9 2 1 6 8 117.
Again you can't put any IP address in here as long as you're going to listen on netcat on that IP address.
So one towards the end and the final part of this command actually here this is the port.
So we're connecting on 4 4 4 4 4.
You can't change that.
Any ports you want to listen to and you want to receive the connection too.
So I'm going to copy all this.
I'm going to go on my rubber ducky
I'm going to paste my code
I'm going to have updates and I'm going to do a convert so I can actually launch the attacks right away.
But before I do that as I said I need to listen on port 4 4 4 4.
So I'm going to go and launch my terminal and I'm going to listen on the fourth Usenet Kathe using the
following command.
And after you put the forth.
So for for's we're going to hit enter and now says that it's listening on 4 4 4 4 4.
So that's perfect.
So I'm going to go back now to my you know taunter menu
and I'm going to go on my rubber ducky and I'm going to hit on the three little buds and execute a tag
as you can see now it's typing in the command.
Why it's so.
Now if I go back so they can show you here and I'm going to go back to my terminal as you can see now
I got abash command prompt and this is on my sex machine and to verify this I'm just going to give you
a PWT and you can see it's in users zoos.
And if I do a you uname
a which will basically just show the kernel information and device information.
Can see that it is its MacBook Pro.
You can see the kernel version and all that.
And basically this is full access to the device so you can run all UNIX commands on my.
So now basically have full access on my MacBook Pro and you can run any Unix command that you want to
do so you can do an ls Toolis files you can navigate so you can go and see the test or you can do anywhere.
Or basically go anywhere you want download upload run other commands and store stuff out services basically
full access to the machine you have now.