This is my favorite part of the course which is the exploitation part so in this section we're going
to talk about a tax that will basically give us full access to the target computer so we will be able
to do anything that we want to the target computer just like what the user can do with their own computer.
We're actually going to use some of the attacks that we learned before combining them with other tasks
to do this and some scenarios and some scenarios will be do and just a full I thought.
We haven't seen before.
We're going to talk about how we can bypass plug ins so we for example if you see a locked computer
or a shut down computer whether it's Windows or Mac OS X we'll see how we can actually log into that
computer even if it uses a password without using a password.
So we're going to be able to do this only by Konev by physically connecting our Android device to that
computer via you speak and then we'll be able to log in to that computer even if it's used using a really
powerful password and it doesn't matter whether it's on Windows or OS X.
We're also going to see a number of keyboard attacks and number of scripts that allow us to gain full
access to Windows computers OSS X and Linux computers so we're going to be attacking all our brain systems
and we're going to see how we can gain full access to these systems using our U.S. v cable.
So basically as soon as you connect your USP cable to our computer you're going to get full access to
it whether it's Linux Windows or us x.
We'll also see how you can do this without even without any physical interaction with Italian computer
using the VDM proxy which will basically backdoor any file that is being downloaded by the target's
person.
We're going to see how we can backdoor that file on the fly.
And once the person runs that file We're going to get full access to their computer.
So you're not even going to need to say anything or enter into interact with the target person you're
just going to wait for them to download the file once they download any kind of file any executable.
Basically we're going to backdoor it on the fly when they're on their file is going to run.
So they want me suspicious and at the same time our backdoor is going to run and we're going to gain
full access to their computer.
We'll also going to see what things we can do after we get that access.
So I'm going to give you a quick look on how to use the interpreter shell and how you can drop to a
Windows shell and all that stuff.
So stay tuned.