Today we'll be talking about a really cool and useful attack that we can use in our Android device.
We're going to see how we can bypass logon screens whether it's Windows or OS X logons.
So you're definitely in when you're doing a contest on a network or a company.
You'll end up in many situations you will have access to computers but a lot of these computers will
be off or they'll be on their logon screen.
So they'll people they'll be assigned out or they lock their computers when they are away.
So this feature is actually really useful.
It will allow you to log into any computer whether it runs Windows or OS X.
Without knowing the password.
It will not modify the password of the existing user.
So when the user comes back they will be able to log in again with their usual password so they will
not know that someone modified their computer or modified their password.
We're going to be using a tool called Con boot can boot can be installed on any USP device or any bootable
device you can install it on.
But in this course because we are talking about penetration testing using your Android device we're
going to see how we can install it on your Android device so we can actually install this on any Android
device.
Doesn't have to be and that Hunter device all they need is an app called Drive Droid which you can download
from the App Store and can boot and download it from their official website.
The only problem is conduit is not a free tool.
It actually costs you $25 to buy.
So we're going to see how we can set up the tool now on your Android device and in the next video we're
connected to our target computer and see how we'll be able to log in without knowing the password
so I've bought the tool myself and I have it installed.
I have the file.
Also when you don't when you buy the tool you get this file which is the cone boot and saltation file.
It actually allows you to install it.
It comes in with an Iraqi that allows you to install it on a USP device or on an ISO image on a CD.
But for now I'm actually going to run it in order to run the cxi you can run it from Windows just double
click it and if you're running it on with Linux you need a program called wine.
So I'm just going to click it here he'll see a normal Windows installation and I'm just going to extract
it here.
So it's in home zoo's downloads convoyed.
And as you can see I have the files here.
And you can actually use the can boot installer to install it on a USP as I said so here you can start
on here.
We are on the CD but I'm not going to be doing that because as I said we're going to be using it on
our Android device.
So I'm going to navigate into cone with USP files.
I'm going to go on use your files here and the file that you want to be using is the can would do it.
I m g.
So is this file.
It's only 1.5 megabytes.
And you can easily send it to your Android phone or you can send this via email by droid by any program
that you want to use.
Just make sure you actually send it to your Android device.
So I sent it actually via e-mail because it's just really easy and I'll show you here how to set it
up on your Android device.
So I'm going to go on the app that I told you you can download from the Apple store.
Again you don't need that Hunter for this.
You can do it on any Android device that runs drive droid.
So I'm going to tap on Dr droite and I'm going to click on the flaws to add an image and I'm going to
say that I'm going to do it from a file because I downloaded it I'm going to call it Khond boots.
And I'm going to click on the this icon and I'm going to go on my file explorer and pick this as you
can see that I have it here.
Can do it.
I am.
So I'm going to tap it there and I'm going to pick the first option.
And just waits for a gun to save it.
And that's it.
Now I have conduits in here.
So all you have to do now whenever.
So don't do this all the time whenever you want to log into a computer that does not have that you don't
have the passwords for that has a log and screen.
All you have to do is Topcon good and select the way that you want to do it.
And I'm going to select three on the here.
So I'm top in that and as you can see it's saying host Hostin image on your screen.
If you go on the notifications you can see that it's telling me that it's just an my conduit image.
So now my Android device is hosting the image.
And as soon as I connected to any laptop it's locked as a USP device with this image.
So we can boot from it.
So in the next video I'll show you I have a Windows computer with a logon with a password.
I'm going to connect it connects my Android device to it and boot from the Android device and we'll
see how we'll be able to log in to the computer without a password.