The next few videos we're going to talk about some contacts that you will need to have a backdoor that
will spawn a shell back to your device.
So I decided to make a video to explain to you how to create a backdoor and how to test this backdoor
so I'm going to explain it was so that in the future when we do more sophisticated attacks I can skip
this step because you know how to do it and you know how to test if it works or not.
So to do this we're actually going to use a tool called Divell evasion.
The reason I'm using this tool is because it creates factors that are not detectable by any antivirus.
So when you create a backdoor and this and this tool the antivirus programs will not detect this as
a threat.
So in order to solve it all you have to do is just apt get install Bill evasion in your terminal and
Cali the process might take some time.
It's going to download around 600 megabytes of packages.
Just every time you asked to do something always say YES YES YES YES YES.
Until the installation is finished.
So it's very straightforward.
Or you have to do is just go here you have to get Misto they'll evey you hit enter and it'll are solved
for you.
Now for me it's saying that it's already installed so I don't need to install it.
Now once you have it installed I'm going to run it using the same command.
So Bill evasion going to hit enter and as you can see now I have 45 notes loaded so that's 45 different
types of doctors that I can create.
If you want to list all these payloads and see what you have you can just type in list to see them that's
all the payload that you can create so far today is on for the next videos we're going to be use and
see as Mr. Patel reverse TTP.
So in order to use this you all you have to do is just type in use 8 because that was number 8.
So now has shown me the options that this has.
And you can use this the same way we were use in me just like in the previous videos the same way you
when you want to change an option you type insert option name and then the value that you want to change
it to.
So you again do this the exact same way.
So for example to set up our IP Address this is our local IP address.
So l host same way that we were doing it with me to exploit all you have to do is type in set host and
put your IP address.
So to see our IP address we type in if configure
as you can see that my IP address is 1 9 2 1 6 8 0 4.
So I'm going to put that here now I'm doing this because we're going to do a verse connection.
So the target machine will be the machine that connects back to us.
Now to make sure that the options are right I'm going to type it in full again and we can see that my
IP address is set up here and then we can see the fourth right here so we have to set this up when we
do the multi-hundred like we did in the previous video.
So now everything's done I'm going to type and generate
and I'm going to type in the name of the file to create So I'm going to call it backdoor.
Now in practice you do you don't want to call your backdoor backdoor.
But for now we're testing so I'm going to call it back door.
And it's created and it's saying it's written to this file.
So my backdoor is stored in user share Bill output compiled backdoor to eat now you get the Yangtze
you can send it to any computer once you're on the cxxviii it will try to connect back to your device
on port 80 80 like we set it up.
So how do we listen to that what we're doing.
We're going to do with the same way we did it when we arrived our first flight option.
So I'm going to run MSF Canso.
I'm going to quit this so I'm going to type in
that exit and then I'm going to write myself.
So.
So the next few steps are going to be exactly the same steps that we did when we did our first flight
option with the idea of what the tag.
So this will basically just allow us to listen on port 80 80 for incoming connections.
So I'm going to use exploits
that I actually don't need to on this come on now because I'm already in it.
Well just to show you how to do it then I'm going to set my payload
to Windows.
Same thing or that we chose one we created the payload so it was Windows interpolator reverse a TTP.
I said the old fart to 88 like we did it before and I'm going I said my host 2 1 9 2 1 6 8 0 14 the
same values that we set up with the back door.
So now we're just making sure that everything is right and everything is right.
So I'm going to type in exploit and now listen in on connections so know I'm going to do now is I'm
going to go I'm going to copy this file to my target Windows machine.
Again this is not a practical attack.
I just want to show you how to create a backdoor and how to test this back there so I'm actually going
to send this file to the target machine and run it from the target machine and we'll see if this works
or not.
So if it works we're going to use it in the future videos to carry out our attacks.
Now I have the file here so I'm going to double click it.
I'm going to run it.
And if we go back here as you can see we got an interpreter session back from this IP which is our target
IP to our IP.
And if we do this info we will see that we are inside the target machine.
This is actually really useful.
So even without this course or without these things that you're going to learn and this course created
a backdoor is really simple and comes in handy into many many situations.
So using villi can create a backdoor that is not detectable by any anti-virus and it can confirm this
using your own anti-virus but please don't upload it to the websites that test for multiple antivirus
is because they usually analyze the backdoor and then it's a want to be undetectable anymore.
So what it creates them undetectable and there are safe Web sites that you can test with.
I'm going to put them and the resources to test your backdoor with and they're not detectable again
by antivirus is that it works to give you a reverse connection.
And it's really small.
So in the future videos we're going to need to use backorders.
I'm going to skip through this step because we already know how to make them.