So in the previous video we show how we can gain an interpreter session on the target machine.
And today I'm just going to show you a few things that you could run or do with your own interpreter
session.
Now again as I said before people take full courses in order to learn how to use with us.
Lloyd so far today we're just going to have a quick look and quick hands on the things that you can
do.
Most important thing keep in mind you can always just type in help and it'll show you all the command
that you can run.
So that's a really helpful thing.
And then you can see what you can do.
So the first thing I'd like to do was something inside the system.
I'd go six ANFO just to get the information of the current system to get to know.
So now we can see that we the computer name is zoos.
It's running Windows 8 x 64 and and the interpreter is 32.
The system language is English you as you can also do an ifconfig to get the interfaces and get their
IP address and all that.
So we can see that it's used in the US we are less careful.
But we can see the MAC address we can see the IP address.
So all this is useful depending on what you want to do with the target machine.
Now we can see that we have another interface here that is not connected.
We have another interface so this is a wired interface.
Again we can see its IP address and its MAC address.
So on other interface right here.
So this is just kind of useful information that we can see of the target machine.
Also you can do as you can see what's your working directory where are you working right now so we're
in C users and this is the user name that we have.
Also we can list all the directories and the files that you have use and Alias.
So this so that's the list all directories that exist in C users and then the users that we're in and
we can see this is all the files that exist and directories.
So let's say you want to go to desktop or you can go see the desktop.
Now if you do PDA and you did see the working directory you see are in desktop.
So we're going to do a list to see all the files that exist in desktop.
And as you can see that there is nothing really except for those of gold I need now let's say this file
is important file that you want to read so you can just read it using cathe command.
Now all these commands again are aren't the help so you can just go through the help and see them and
now you can see what the 12. only contains.
Now let's say you want to download this file and save it to your hard drive.
You can just do download this self-taught any and it's downloaded it now for me.
So if I go into my working into my home folder as you can see that I can see I have a file called sculped
ID
Lets say you want to upload something.
Now again I have here I have a file called said that the Axion has not it just has a I'm going to upload
the file but in practice you'd be uploading more dangerous things like viruses kill ogres reverse Yeo's
stuff like that.
So for now we're just going to upload something simple so we're going to do upload that do it takes
the and now the file is uploaded.
If we do a list we can see it right here if we do I have to make sure that it contains.
It was uploaded properly.
It will see that it actually contains AAA.
Now if this was an executable you can execute it using execute.
And then you put the file name which is the.
Now this will give me an error now because it's not an executable saying it's not valid Win32 application
but if it was executed on the target machine.
Now this is just like file handling.
Uploading doing stuff like that.
Let's go again on the help and see what else we can do.
So again you can even get scripts and you can get plugins that you use with interpolator.
I'm not going to go through them in this course.
So let me see what else.
So you'll be using to use and run through on plugins or no plugins.
And so these were the commands that we were using the file system commands see the upload download.
You can make directories you can remove used in our search.
So basically just you just put the command name on the command that you want to run.
You also have your network commands right here so you can type in R.P. to get the AARP cash or display
interfaces and although we saw ifconfig how to display the interfaces these are the system command so
we use the execute to execute an executable.
You can clear events log where you can get the process number that we're working right now.
Now you can get the user ID.
So if you do get the it will show you the process that you're working on can do a PSA to see all the
processes that's running right now.
And something cool that you can do so because you're running now on this process are 3 7 8 8 and you
can see that it is a suspicious thing.
So it's called partial.
What you can do is you can do emigrate migrate so you can migrate to a different process that is less
suspicious than the process that you're using right now.
So what we can do is we can look look for Explorer dirty.
And as you can see that it is running on to nine to eight so in order to migrate to that process we're
going to do great 2 2 9 8 and this will basically move our show from powerslide into ex-parte RTX.
So let's get the idea.
And as you can see that we're actually running now through explorer.
If someone looks at the processes we're going to show up as if we're running from the Explorer or not
from the partial We saw the system info and still talking is an attempt to steal the token can use shell
which will give you a command show I'll show that to you later.
It'll basically just give you a Windows Comanche and you can run Windows command through it can kill
processes you can do reboot.
You can modify registry so you can just keep playing around with it and see what you can do.
So let's have a look on this option so this will basically allow you to insert the key logger which
will record any keystroke typed on the keyboard.
So in order to do this it's really simple it's just keys can start and that will start recording any
keystroke I put on my target computer.
So I'm going to go on say for example Google dot com.
Actually let's go to G-mail and start to sign in now.
It doesn't matter if it's using CTP as or if it's used in the latest security
because it's going to record our physical keyboard strikes so it doesn't matter if it's used the CPS
or not it's actually not sniffing anything.
So let's put the password as one two three four five six seven eight.
And when I come back here and do a quick scan
we can see that we went on Google.
We typed in return.
We went to G-mail we typed in return it went down down down down down up return because I actually didn't
type in say that as a security at all.
I just selected it from there.
But we recorded.
The password was 1 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 7 8.
And then we had to return and not stop this we can just do Keef's can stop that and stop it.
So we can you can experiment with this.
There's a lot of other plug ins that you can do you can actually inject or upload interpretor sessions
that work as services that will start every time the computer starts.
So you can upload one like this and have it running in the background every time your target computer
starts so you will have access to it anytime you want.
You can play with this you can do a lot of things that are really cool and powerful attacks using it.
But I'm not going to talk about all of them again because as I said you'll need a full course for this
and this course is basically just talking about penetration testing use in Android.
One more feature I want to show you is if you just go on show it will go into Windows.
Also this is a normal Windows Shell as you can see see windows so you can run Windows commands so you
can do dare to list stuff you can do cd to see the so see the door does you go back see you go again
then you can go see the users and do any Windows commands that you want to do.