So now though we know how to create a backdoor and how we can listen for connections coming from that
backdoor.
Today we're going to combine all number of things that we learn before in order to launch a powerful
attack.
So we're going to do is we're going to do a fake download attack.
So basically the target person so some person and it that we are connected to is going to download and.
We're going to replace this with our backdoor so that the person once he tries to run the XP that he
downloaded he will actually run our backdoor and instead of the programs that they think they downloaded.
So we're now going to need to physically connect to their computer.
We're not going to need to fool them or send them anything or tell them all.
Download this up or download this thing.
They're willingly going to download say a program that they want to download as their downloads and
it's will going to be the man in the middle.
So we're going to do A.R.T. poison ink like we learned before using Zanti.
We're going to replace the file that they're downloaded with our backdoor.
And then when they run the file We're going to get.
We'll Very get full access to their tablet computer.
We actually did this whole attack scenario when we were talking about Zanti but instead of replacing
the downloaded file with the backdoor we actually replaced it with a calculator.
And when I ran it on the target machine the person ran a calculator instead of the program that they
downloaded.
Now that wasn't really useful like to place a program with a calculator for you replace it with a back
door.
It's much more useful because we're going to gain full access to the target computer.
So what we're going to do is we've already done the first two steps.
We have our backdoor.
And I've sent it to my the Tanter device and it's there now and listen on connections and I'm already
listening on connections here.
So I'm just going to do exploits and I'm listening on my back there that was created in the previous
video.
So now all we're going to do is I'm going to become the man in the middle then I'm going to launch the
interception feature to intercept the downloaded files.
So let's go to our next Hunter device.
I'm going to go on Zanti
and I'm going to go on my target device and that is my Windows device right here so it's 1 9 2 6 8 0
11 that I'm going to go on man in the middle.
We did all of this before so it's the exact same steps.
The only difference is that we're going to use our backdoor in this case.
Now I'm going to go on the interceptor.
I'm going to I click on this gear icon
then I'm going to make sure that the extension right here is selected as Yves and my file is selected
so I'm going to go on them next file.
I'm going to go use an S file explorer.
I'm going to select my backdoor right here so backdoor that you actually select the first method
now everything is done.
So all I'm going to do is I'm going to enable my interceptor option by typing on the up and now it's
on.
And now I'm going to tap on the on self-pride to enable the man in the middle attack which will basically
put me in the middle of the connection.
And so now that every time that the target person tries to download any XP it will be replaced by the
X-C that we selected in our intercept download option.
So let's go to our windows machine and try to download something and see what happens.
So that's go to be dot.com
then let's say I'm going to search for seven zip.
Then the person is going to go to their downloads page try to download the latest version of Sony's
going to say save it.
Now remember that the backdoor that we created is actually undetectable by antivirus.
So as you can see now it's downloaded 7 0 1 5 0 5.
The only suspicious thing is that you see there is no icon on it.
It's not going to be detectable by antivirus is.
And when you're on it the Windows will tell you that it has an unknown publisher
wants its Ron.
It's not going to run the actual unzip it's going to on our backdoor.
So this would be a bit suspicious as well when the person is going to double click it as if it's not
going to work the program that they expect to work.
But when you go back here you will see that we got full access and we have therapy session on the target
device so we can do a system for and we'll see that we have access to this Windows 8 machine.
Now as I said there's two suspicious things.
The first thing that has no icon.
The second thing is that when the person double click it their program is not actually going to work.
So they're not going to see their program they might suspect that something went wrong.
Now in the next video we're going to do is we're going to learn how we backdoor these files on the fly.
So once someone tries to download like this we're going to backdoor their program that they're downloading
on the fly and our back door to it all when they run it.
Their program will work.
And our backdoor will work at the same time so that they won't be suspicious that something went wrong.