So and the previous video we saw how we can replace a file that is being downloaded by a target computer
with another file and we replace any X with a backdoor.
So one of the first lines that he asks that we gained full access to their computer of course we had
to do this while we were in the middle.
The problem is when the what we actually did we replaced the file that was being downloaded.
So when the person ran the file the file that worked did not produce the result that the user was expecting.
For example let's say the user was downloading 7 zip when they double clicked it.
Our back to around 7 zip didn't run.
So the user might suspect us something went wrong.
Well they can manually go ahead before the user downloads anything try to backdoor 7 zip and replace
it with 7.
But you never know what the target person is going to download anyway.
So what we're going to use today is a proxy called the backdoor factory proxy where this proxy will
do is on the fly as the person decides to download the file whether the file is an easy or easy.
It's going to back up this file.
So it's going to use the same file that it's been downloaded and our backdoor to it.
So when the person runs it is going to look like as if they are running their actual file and the actual
file will work it's not going to be corrupt and our backdoor is going to run at the same time.
This will work against Windows OS X machines.
So the first thing you want to do is you want to go on your configuration file for the backdoor factory
and modify and add your IP address in there.
So let me go there and show you.
So we're going to put the IP address where we want to get the show and previous videos we were actually
sent in the show to our the next machine.
Today we're going to get the shell here on our hunter machine just because we're not connecting it to
USP it's going to be a wireless attack and I'll show you how to do it.
It's exactly the same.
We're going to use with us voice and multi-hundred to listen on a port.
So we're going to be run the exact same commands that we run on Linux in order to listen for a.
Now before we do that I go to the configuration file.
So I'll show you what it is.
I already have it open here so I have a route so far here downloaded from the paste are free and simple
and works.
So data local Karlee.
If you see
bact or proxied and then click on the configuration file.
Now I'm not going to change anything in this file.
The only thing that I'm going to change is my current IP address because this proxy backdoor is any
downloaded zip or eat or wrocław is executables what you want to do if you start a multi-hundred or
on only one file.
You're only going to receive one type of shelves so you will not be able to receive shelves for different
operating systems.
So what this does it actually comes in with with a test flight script that runs a number of hands are
instances simultaneously so that you can listen on different parts for different operating systems.
So you can see here if you scroll down you'll see that it's going to ask you to put your IP address
for the next payloads for the Windows payloads.
Now fix that for the Windows payloads and I put my IP address which is 1 9 2 1 6 8 17.
This is my IP address of this net Hunter device.
And as you can see here I have that on here for this device.
And also note the Fords and you can see that it's asking you for Macintosh as well.
And you can also modify the type of payload that's going to be executed or that's going to be used for
each of these operating systems.
So in order to listen to the parts you can run the script that comes in with back to our factory use
in this command so we're going to do most of console are that use the scripts but as you can see here
now today I'm not going to use the script because it runs a number of instances and is going to put
a lot of load on my hunter device.
So I'm actually going to use a manual multi-hundred like we did it before and I'm only going to listen
for the Windows connections because I'm going to be targeting a Windows device so I'm only going to
be listening for the Windows connections for the X 86 which is this one 1 4 8 8 4 4 3.
So I actually don't need this file right now but I'm just showing you if you want to use the script
you would put your IPs in there and then you run the script using this command.
So for me I'm just going to do it manually.
I'll do it next.
But before I do that I'm going to do.
I'm going to start my back backdoor factory.
And after I do that we're going to do the same what we did with the SSL strip.
We're going to use IP tables to redirect any packet coming on port 80.
We're going to redirect it to 88.
We're going to do this because our factory runs on port 88.
You can change just from the same configuration here that we were looking at just a second ago but I'm
leaving it at 88 so we're going to redirect any packet coming at 80 to 88.
So that's our factory can analyze it if it finds that it is an executable It's a backdoor for us and
then we can hide the target's computer.
So this is what I'm going to do next.
Let's go on my Kelly machine.
I'm going to go on my terminal's
and I'm going to run box just as simple as I'll give it two seconds to load and that's it.
Back to our factories is working now the next thing you want to do.
As I said is run IP tables in order to redirect any packet coming on port 80 to 88.
We're back to our factories running.
So I have the command here and I'm going to just have a..
And you don't see any error messages that means the command was ran successfully.
Now I'm going to run my test flight in order to listen.
So I'm going to type in MSF console in order to listen on the forward for Windows machines.
Now again if you're if you're not recording videos and there isn't much pressure on your laptop on your
device then you can do.
You can run it using this command but for me I'm going to just do it manually and only listen for Windows
machines.
If you use this command you're going to be listening to all different types of machines that you can
target using backdoor factory the method that I'm explaining right now you can run it from Cali to the
next and you can run from any computer given that you install the programs.
Now Canada Next comes in with backdoor factory installed.
So if you learned this on your Android you can actually perform it using another Linux machine.
You can do the exact same attack
OK.
Now this place is working and we're going to do the exact same commands that we did when we were trying
to use multi handler on the Linux and the previous videos.
Except we're just typing them here and Android.
So I'm already in multi-hundred But I type the command for you so you know what to do.
So it's use the exploit more to learn than you set your.
No to Windows.
Peter rivers if you don't make make sure you have the same payload and the configuration files that
we saw before.
Now I'm just going to show options because they have all the options right.
I think now if you want to change an option you just do it the same way that we did it before so they
just do said you put the option name and the value.
So if you want to for example change the host you just do set host and then you put the IP you know
everything is right for me right here.
So it's the exact same way we explained it before.
So I'm just going to leave it.
I'm going to do exploit and this is listening on the port so everything's perfect right now and I have
my backdoor factory running here.
So and I've already redirected any requests to port from Port 80 to 88.
You are back there factor is running.
So everything is perfect.
We are only to do one step which is becoming the man in the middle.
So you have the degree of choice to choose where how you want to be the man in the middle you can do
it.
Why make a fake access point to use in a manner you can do.
Are people listening you can do a hazy idea about us we attack.
For me I'm going to do IRP poisoning using Zanti because it's the easiest way so I'm going to go back
and I'm going to search for laptops
and I can see my device here the windows.
It's called zoos.
So I'm going to tap on it.
I'm going to go to mine in the middle like we did before and as you can see all the options are off.
I just want to point and redirect the flow packets through my device.
So now everything is perfect and I'm just going to go again through a quick review of what we are doing
ARPU poisoning our target.
So we're fooling the target machine to send any packet to our device instead of the router.
Once the packets come to our device we're redirecting them from Port 80 to 88 to use an IP tables on
AT&amp;T.
We have another factor you work in.
So it's going to detect if there is any excuse woes if there is it's going to ask us to if we want to
backdoor it if we say yes the executable is going to be backdoor and then the person can download it
when they downloaded the executable was going to work exactly like expected but at the same time it's
going to run our backdoor which will try to connect back to us on Meet us both using the reverse handler.
So I'm here on my target machine and I'm going to go to 7c website and I'm going to go to the download
page and I'm going to try to download Sivan's for my computer and when I do that I'm going to go back
to my college machine and I'm here at the window where you can download.
We're back to our factories working.
And as you can see it's it's the second that the person is trying to download an executable and it usually
shows you caves.
Caves are gaps in the executable that we can inject our backdoor and now in this particular area we
don't have a free cave that is enough for our acts for our backdoor or for our payload.
So we have two options we can use jumping.
So it's going to use smaller gaps and divide the payload into small small parts or you can just append
it or added to the end of the file.
So I'm going to choose to append and it's going to inject the back door as you can see expansion.
The back door with the executable and it's offering it to the person now as you can see the person is
being offered to download seven zip.
So I'm going to click on Save and that has downloaded it for me.
So I'm just going to show it in folders before I run it.
And as you can see before seven zip did not have the icon of seven zip.
When we when we replaced it with a backdoor.
And now when I run it it's going to run the back door and seven zip.
So the person will be actually able to install 7 0 on their device.
I'm going to say Ron So as you can see it's actually trying to run 7 0.
I'm going to say your trusted and this will install it for me.
Now if I go back here and I'm going to go to my YOU MEET US voice what I'm listening for connections
and as you can see that I've got an interpreter session open 2 1 9 2 1 6 8 1:17 which is me and it's
coming from and 94.
So I can do a quick system info to confirm
as you can see it's the device that we're targeting it's use Windows 8 x 64.
So this was just another scenario that shows you how we can combine the things that we learned so far
in order to run very powerful attacks.