Today we're going to talk about another exploitation method that we can do use that Hunter before we
were able to fool a computer when we connected with use and you asked me and we told the computer that
we are a network device.
When we did this we force all the traffic through our network device which allowed us to read all the
packets intercept them and modify them or do whatever that we want to do as a man in the middle.
We did that in the U.S. we attack.
Now today we're going to do hate I.D. keyboard attack.
So in this attack we're going to fool the computer and tell tell that computer that we are a keyboard
instead of it that we are a network device.
When we do that as we will be able to sense physical keystrokes to that computer as well.
There won't be physical but we're going to program our Android device to send keystrokes to that computer
but they will appear as if they're being typed physically.
This will allow us to bypass the auto run feature and who will allow us to do run any command that we
want to run on the target machine.
So we can't run any Windows commands.
We can gain full access to that computer we'll see that and the next video or you can just add a username
and password and then remotely log into that computer which is what we're going to do in this video.
So we're going to program our Android device.
As I said we're going to add commands so we're going to use to command the first command is to add a
user.
And the second command is to add that user to the administrators.
So let's go ahead and first before I actually execute the attack I want to show you some of the configurations
that you need to do first so that the attack works successfully.
So the first thing you want to do is go to an app called USV keyboard.
Now this comes in pre-installed with Kaleena next.
And when you run it for the first time it's going to ask you to install the kernel.
So say yes it's going to install it automatically for you.
Now here I don't need to do that because I've already done it before.
I'm not asking me to do it.
Now once you do that go back to settings and go to developer options.
And make sure that you be debugging is enabled.
And as you can see I have it enabled here.
Then go to storage and click on these three little dots and go and make sure that MPP is enabled.
Now once you have these two things enable you to go and we can start the attack.
So I'm going to launch Kalli menu and I'm going to navigate through the keyboard the thuck and this
is the first flight is what allows you to gain full access to the target computer and hack it.
So I'm going to leave that for the next video and I'm going to go to the windows and the option.
So here you put the commands that you want to run on the target machine.
And as you can see that I have to come are surrounded.
Now these are Windows commands.
You can run them through the terminal you can add any command that you want here.
And it's a run.
So if you actually do this command on Windows it'll either use a name on Windows and password as we're
doing it here.
But we're actually going to program our computer and then can our device and then connect it to the
computer and these commands will be executed automatically.
So I'm just going to change the user name here to.
Now if you're doing penetration testing you probably want to use a different name
so and the password is 1 2 3 4 5 6.
So that's all good.
We're going to do updates and lots of data.
So everything is perfect.
Now what I'm going to do is I'm going to go.
I'll show you here my Windows device right here and I'm going to connect my Nexus device to this machine
using you and me.
So now my device is connected and I'm going to go on my hunter machine right here and I'm going to click
on these little three dots and hit execute.
Attack get to go back quickly to my Windows machine and as you can see that these commands are actually
now being executed automatically.
So I'm not physically typing these commands they're just being around really quickly.
So as you can see that the commands got executed automatically.
I didn't actually use Kamar So the command prompt got opened a Randi to come up so I wanted the net
user zayd.
And then the addition to the administrators group.
So we actually now have a username and password on a target machine and we achieved this only by connected
our next device to that machine.
So all we can do now is remotely logging into that machine using the remote desktop.
So I downloaded the Microsoft remote desktop from the plaister
Well you actually need to sign up sign out to this account first.
So I'm going to sign out
and then enter here I'm going to add a new device.
I'm going to say it's a desktop and then I'm going to put the IP address
which is 1 9 2 6 a.
I'm going to save up the device going to try to connect.
Now you can do this from any device.
You can do this from one to the next device or macrolides or Windows and other Windows device.
Well we're just doing it from Android because we're teaching penetration testing from Android devices.
So it's going to ask you if you trust that computer I'm going to say yes no problem connect to.
So the user name is Zayde
that password is 1 2 3 4 5 6.
Connect.
Now as you can see trying to plug me in as a
so I have full access to the Windows machine remotely access use the remote desktop using the username
that we did.
So basically this attack allows you to run any Windows command that you can preprogram And once you
connect your device to a Windows or to a device used in U.S. be these attacks will automatically run
as if they're physically being typed on a keyboard.