OK so we saw before how we can connect our Android phone physically to a laptop and then have it to
pretend to be a keyboard and then program the Android device to send certain commands to this laptop
so we saw how we can add a username and password with a password and add the user name to the administrators
and then remotely connect to the target laptop from another computer.
Or from our Android device.
Now the problem is the privileges on the logged in user does not allow you to add new user.
Another problem is a Remote Desktop might not might not be enabled on the target computer.
So if you actually want to gain full access to the target computer you're better off using the power
split option.
This option allow you to get a reverse shield so you get full access to the target's computer and you
will then be able to escalate your privileges change your privileges maybe to administrator you can
add usernames and passwords from this show.
You can change the shell to the NCCL and then you'll see everything like most desktop you can do much
more things you can start and I think you basically get a reverse interpreter handler which is part
of the meta both you will see what the other means now.
Basically it gives you a very powerful shell that gives you full access to the salvias computer.
So the main attack method is the same so we will be using our Android device to fool the target computer
as a keyboard.
So we're going to have to connect our Android device physically to the tablet computer.
Once we do this we will get a reverse show on another machine.
Now where we get the Universe will depend on what we want to do.
We can actually do it get the reverse show on the Android or we can get the reverse show on another
computer.
Certainly won't see anywhere else that we want.
All you need to use is a tool called me that's Floyd.
So I'm using calisthenics right here as a virtual machine and I have my terminal open and I'm going
to show you how we are going to set up our handler so we can make our Android device to the target machine.
It's going to do a reverse connection instead of us connecting to the with computer from Cali.
We're going to program our Android device to send commands to the Windows machine to make it connect
to the kalee.
We're doing a reverse connection this way so that we can bypass firewalls.
So this is my Callimachi and this is where I'm going to get my reverse connection so you can run these
commands on any computer or device that has metal plate installed on it.
Again you can do this on your Android device in the terminal.
You can do these commands and you get the shield back into your Android.
But I'm doing it here on a different computer because in this scenario when you actually want to connect
your computer your device to another computer you will look suspicious.
Then using your device and you'll have a terminal and stuff on your device.
So the best stealth way to do it is you connect your Android device to the computer and then the show
goes back to another laptop somewhere else.
So this is what we're actually doing.
This is a virtual machine right here.
The first command I'm going to run is to run dimittis bloweth console and it's MSF console.
This will take some time to load up the whole the whole plate framework.
Now with us bloat is a huge framework that can be used into many many different things.
So today we're only looking on how to set up a reverse handler and get a reverse connection on its.
So in order to do that we're going to do use exploit multiday there.
So this is the auxilary that we're going to use.
It's called exploit multi handler.
Then I'm going to type in Show Options now you can run show options at any stage to see the options
that you have or you can set.
So you can see that the module options are these.
And the payload is set this is correctly so you might not actually have the payload set up correctly.
The payload is the type of code that will ponder verst connection.
So in my case we're going to either use a reverse hasty CPS or a very safe city.
So I'm going to send the payload I'm actually just going to change it to show you how to change the
payload because when you run it for the first time you're going to have a blank for payloads.
So I'm just going to show you how to change the payload.
Now you can do this changing the payload is the same no matter what you are doing even if you're on
a different tack.
So you just go said haloed those interpretor reverse HTP and we can see that the payload will change.
Now if you want to change the airport or the host it's the same for me to change them.
So if you change the host is the listening host.
So it's the IP of this current machine.
I'm just going to see what's the IP of this machine using ifconfig.
So that's just a Linux command to see the IP.
So my IP is 1 9 2 1 6 8 0 14.
So I'm going to do it again.
So it's the same format.
You type in set and then you type in the name of the variable that you want to change.
So the variable for me now is I'll host and I want to set it to 1 9 2 1 6 8 0 4 2 Okay.
So I'm going to do show options again to make sure that all the options are correct.
So we're using the.
They have their windows with their fraternally very safe.
This is my IP and this is the fourth and the target is Windows or wild card so everything's perfect.
Now once you're ready we're going to type in exploit as you can see this doesn't really do anything.
It just sits and waits for connections.
Come on 4 4 4 4 4.
So it's not going to do anything.
It's not going to try to hike or run any exploits.
It's basically just waiting for any device to connect to it on 4 4 4 4 4.
Again you can run these commands on any device that has meters Floyd including your net Hunter device
if you want to do it from it.
Now we're all set.
Everything is ready.
So we're going to go on our hunter machine
some minor Hunter home and I'm going out.
First thing I'm going to navigate to my ex-service control and I'm going to turn on my apache server
by tapping on it.
So Apache is on now then I'm going to go to my page.
The keyboard attack and I'm going to make sure that all these options are correct.
So the first thing is our IP address and that is correct 1 9 3 1 6 8 0 14 that's the IP where the connection
will be sent to.
So that's the IP of the Kalli machine that we run with smote on and it's the same you put in the same
IP as the one that we put as the host here.
So as you can see that my host is one of six age 14 and it's the same as this one second option is my
forte.
Again make sure it's the same so it's 4 4 4 4.
The third option the payload.
Again make sure it's the same windows interpreter Reverse-Flash CTP and then the last one is the IP.
Now this should be the IP of your Android device and it's the same as what we saw in the home menu.
So it's 1 9 2 1 6 8 0 8 and that's why we turned on our Apache server.
So Apache is a web server and that's where the payload is going to be stored.
So once we execute the attack the payload will be downloaded from the Android device.
It will be executed on the windows the target machine and it will send that connection to the machine
that runs with us.
Floyds which is in this case the Callimachi and the virtual machine so I'm going to hit on these three
little dots and I'm going to hit on execute attack and I'm going to navigate quickly to my windows.
And as you can see now these are these commands that are actually being typed automatically the same
way that what happened when we ran our CMBS or page I.D. keyboard the tag when we typed in that user
or user or whatever.
Now this will actually download the payload from the Android device execute the payload in this machine
and then spawn a show on this machine.
And as we can see we have access to the target's Windows machine so we can see that we have a session
one open.
It's come into this IP which is our IP and it's coming from 1 9 2 1 6 8 0 2 which is my Windows device
and now I have basically full access and full control over the target machine using my interpreter.
Now I will give you a quick showcase of what you can do once you're in this situation.